{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B00005V3D9","answerTime":"2012-10-12","unixTime":1350025200.0,"question":"can test results be downloaded","answer":"yes did not even know this when brought it with me to my first doctors appointment with diabetes specialist she downloaded it right away and had print out chart of testing that did over the past several months was amazed","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"accu chek compactplus diabetes monitoring care kit all in one convenience","title":"ACCU-CHEK Compact Plus Meter Kit","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":19049},"price":74.31,"brand":"Accu Chek"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B00006JHQC","answerTime":"2012-12-29","unixTime":1356768000.0,"question":"are these strips coded","answer":"these are the new strips and they do not need to be coded","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"virtually pain free testing 100 strips vials of 50","title":"FreeStyle Test Strips - 100 ea","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":30329},"price":59.94,"brand":"Freestyle"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0000CFXSN","answerTime":"2012-12-29","unixTime":1356768000.0,"question":"are they the same as the bluettes bought about 20 years ago they just got hole in them the new bluettes don look the same","answer":"wasn happy with the recent bluettes that purchased mainly because of the lack of texture on the hand area found dropped things much more and consequently had some breakage the true blues are just as thick as the bluettes and have little texture on the hand portion which seems to make all the difference plus they come in fun colors","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"true blues are quite possibly the most comfortable pair of household gloves you will ever own their tough vinyl shell generous cotton liner and snug fit allow true blues to resist hot water and household chemicals saving your hands from drying and cracking because true blues are vinyl they won crack like regular latex gloves true blues are latex free and are machine washable making them the only household gloves you will ever need available in small to extra large","title":"True Blues Large Blue Ultimate Household Gloves","salesRank":{"Kitchen & Dining":11404},"price":10.95,"brand":"Star Kitchen"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0000CFXSL","answerTime":"2012-12-29","unixTime":1356768000.0,"question":"are they the same as the bluettes bought about 20 years ago they just got hole in them the new bluettes don look the same","answer":"wasn happy with the recent bluettes that purchased mainly because of the lack of texture on the hand area found dropped things much more and consequently had some breakage the true blues are just as thick as the bluettes and have little texture on the hand portion which seems to make all the difference plus they come in fun colors","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"true blues are quite possibly the most comfortable pair of household gloves you will ever own their tough vinyl shell generous cotton liner and snug fit allow true blues to resist hot water and household chemicals saving your hands from drying and cracking because true blues are vinyl they won crack like regular latex gloves true blues are latex free and are machine washable making them the only household gloves you will ever need available in small to extra large","title":"True Blues Small Blue Ultimate Household Gloves","salesRank":{"Kitchen & Dining":4628},"price":10.95,"brand":"Star Kitchen"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B00012NJJG","answerTime":"2012-12-21","unixTime":1356076800.0,"question":"are these vegeterian does not seem to say on the label","answer":"these are not vegetarian ordered them thinking that they were only to find out that they have gelatin","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"natural vitamin is an essential nutrient and is the body primary fat soluble antioxidant vitamin provides nutritional support for the cardiovascular system skin and the immune system it helps fight cell damaging free radicals that cause oxidative stress in the body which may contribute to the premature aging of cells this formulation provides natural vitamin as alpha tocopherol plus beta delta and gamma tocopherols it is offered in oil based softgels to promote optimal absorption and assimilation","title":"Solgar - Vitamin E, 400 IU, 100 softgels","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":7465},"price":12.73,"brand":"Solgar"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0001TRZ94","answerTime":"2012-12-15","unixTime":1355558400.0,"question":"can you take this internally","answer":"mixed it with some water and drank it no problem read the back of the bottle don think it is supposed to be rubbed on hope this helps","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"burdock root arctium lappa has been traditionally used as mild tonic due to its range of beneficial properties today the herb is recognized for promoting detoxification nature answer capsules feature the highest quality of organic responsibly wildcrafted or cultivated herbs which maintain the naturally occurring constituents found in the plant they are carefully selected and finely milled micronized allowing faster absorption by the body manufactured to cgmp current good manufacturing practices standards free of synthetic ingredients","title":"Nature's Answer Burdock Root, 90-Count","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":128914},"price":4.57,"brand":"Nature&#39;s Answer"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B00028OSSU","answerTime":"2012-12-20","unixTime":1355990400.0,"question":"do these tablets taste like mint can tell if peppermint has been added","answer":"don think you can really taste anything at all it still has very mild papaya taste it is not off putting or strong by any means","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"papaya enzyme with chlorophyll by american health products 600 chewable papaya enzyme with chlorophyll 600 chewable product our famous blend with chlorophyll is the perfect after meal supplement to help support and maintain daily digestive health we combine the finest quality of freshly ripened papaya fruit with papain amylase and protease enzymes which aid in the digestion of proteins and carbohydrates while encouraging proper nutrient absorption our formula offers the ideal choice to help with inefficient digestion take this delicious papaya enzyme regularly to promote gastrointestinal wellness while helping to reduce bad taste and sweeten breath the after meal supplement 100 natural digestive enzyme helps with inefficient digestion promotes nutrient absorption great tasting vegetarian formula with chlorophyll to freshen breath and reduce bad taste suggested use as dietary supplement for adults chew three tablets following meal one to three times daily or dissolve one","title":"American Health Papaya Enzyme With Chlorophyll Chewable -- 600 Chewable Tablets","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":4374},"price":12.93,"brand":"American Health"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0002IHF1M","answerTime":"2012-12-07","unixTime":1354867200.0,"question":"are these now foods lysine 500 mg vegetarian capsules or rough tablets","answer":"they are vegetarian formula but are white hard tablet but with smooth surfaces the tablet is long 16 wide and deep","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"lysine is an essential amino acid which means your body cannot manufacture it it must be obtained through the diet or by supplementation lysine is one of the most well known amino acids and is an essential component of all proteins","title":"Now Foods L-Lysine 500mg,  250 Tablets","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":5053},"price":10.98,"brand":"Now Foods"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0002KHTPM","answerTime":"2012-12-14","unixTime":1355472000.0,"question":"does these replacement brush heads fit my oral professional care 8850","answer":"just noticed this on the package does not fit vitality sonic sonic complete pulsonic cross action power since this is an oral product assume it fits all their other models hope this is helpful","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Oral-B Professional Prowhite Replacement Brush Head 1 Count","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":14561},"price":8.99,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0002KHTG6","answerTime":"2012-12-14","unixTime":1355472000.0,"question":"does these replacement brush heads fit my oral professional care 8850","answer":"just noticed this on the package does not fit vitality sonic sonic complete pulsonic cross action power since this is an oral product assume it fits all their other models hope this is helpful","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Oral-B Professional Prowhite Replacement Brush Head 3 Count","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":609},"price":22.99,"brand":"Oral B"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B00065TIPC","answerTime":"2012-10-23","unixTime":1350975600.0,"question":"the ingredients aren listed wish the label was posted is there any sweetener in the natural flavor including stevia","answer":"the 100 natural whey protein powder does not contain any artificial sweeteners this is only the natural flavor version the flavored ones do contain sweeteners though not sure which ones you can see copy of the nutritional label at this site url here is list of the ingredients whey protein isolate natural french vanilla flavor soy lecithin xanthan gum contains milk and soy there is no yeast wheat gluten preservatives artificial color artificial flavor or artificial sweeteners","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"biochem 100 whey protein contains 100 pure ultra filtered micro filtered uf mf whey protein isolate the finest quality and most easily assimilated whey protein isolate on the market the micro filtration method isolates the natural whey proteins in highly concentrated form without fat this process leaves 99 of the peptides undamaged and undenatured free of artificial hormones including rbst and rbgh 100 whey protein is rich in the highly bioactive fractions glycomacropeptide and beta lactoglobulin immunoglobulin glycopeptides and lactoferrin plus amino acids that support muscle tissue","title":"100% Whey Powder Chocolate Fudge - 15.4 oz - Powder","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":81070},"price":18.14,"brand":"Bio Chem"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B00075M1WI","answerTime":"2012-10-25","unixTime":1351148400.0,"question":"is it 12 24 as mentioned in the product features and the picture shown or is it 12 inches as mentioned in the product description below","answer":"it 12 24","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"sunbeam heating pad with ultraheattechnology offers an effective way to take good care of yourself and maintain an active life this heating pad also features new arthritic controller for ease of use","title":"Sunbeam 764-511 King Size Moist\/Dry Heating Pad","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":15830},"price":18.82,"brand":"Sunbeam"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0007VNZU4","answerTime":"2012-11-30","unixTime":1354262400.0,"question":"is this item designed for fiberglass tubes have jacuzzi tube surrounded by tile one side will be in the tube and the other side on tile","answer":"john don think it would matter bought this for my mom and she has ceramic bathtub just make sure it is flush on both sides and it not real thick so you can get good grip on it when you tighten it","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"the bathtub bar that locks to the side of your tub allows for you to get in and out of your tub it has crank style locking device that attaches to tub walls up to inches wide the unit is inches wide it is equipped with rubber pads to protect the tub walls and weighs only 05 pounds 250 pound weight capacity all coated steel design for durability","title":"Medline Bathtub Bar, Locks to Side of Tub","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":2345},"price":32.95,"brand":"Medline"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0008D7VC4","answerTime":"2012-12-26","unixTime":1356508800.0,"question":"is it the trioxon knee support","answer":"afraid don know what that is bought it because of the magnets which seem to promote healing and circulation for me as well as suppost the knee","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"two concentric circle bioflex magnets are incorporated into nylon backed neoprene knee brace with dual nylon web straps and two hook and loop closures","title":"Bioflex Magnetic Knee Support - Large\/X-Large","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":300190},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B00095VINE","answerTime":"2012-12-23","unixTime":1356249600.0,"question":"is this cuff really large cuff need large cuff for accurate reading","answer":"this is regular size cuff for regular sized adult to get an accurate blood pressure on large adult you will need to order an extra large cuff regular sized cuff will not give accurate readings on really large arm proper fit is important for an accurate reading suggest you look on another site if there are none on amazon make sure that it comes with guage included unless you already have one and stethoscope","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"the prosphyg 760c is our most popular aneroid it is the model of choice for demanding institutions","title":"American Diagnostic Corporation Prosphyg 760C, Black, Small Adult","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":36807},"price":25.39,"brand":"American Diagnostic"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0009MFUPO","answerTime":"2012-11-29","unixTime":1354176000.0,"question":"will hq9 replacement heads fit model 8240xl","answer":"yes chatted with represenative","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Philips Norelco HQ9 SpeedXL Replacement Heads","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":206},"price":26.7,"brand":"Philips"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0009VU16I","answerTime":"2012-12-23","unixTime":1356249600.0,"question":"is this cuff really large cuff need large cuff for accurate reading","answer":"this is regular size cuff for regular sized adult to get an accurate blood pressure on large adult you will need to order an extra large cuff regular sized cuff will not give accurate readings on really large arm proper fit is important for an accurate reading suggest you look on another site if there are none on amazon make sure that it comes with guage included unless you already have one and stethoscope","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"the 760 series features bull contemporary black enamel 300mmhg no pin stop manometer provides day in day out dependability provides day in day out dependability bull adcufftm nylon cuff with adc 8217 proprietary size guidetm marking system prevents mis cuffing bull dip molded latex inflation bladder withstands heavy use bull chrome plated brass air release valve bull leatherette carrying case with durable nylon zipper bull assembled inspected and packaged in the from foreign components bull lifetime calibration warranty coverage two year part warranty coverage adc medical instruments and accessories have been carefully designed to meet the rigorous demands of the most discriminating healthcare professionals throughout the world adc products are manufactured from the finest materials with an uncompromising concern for quality exhaustive inspection of every item by adc factory trained quality control staff ensures strict compliance with adc standards for performance and durability and the commitment to manufacturing excellence is backed by the industry 8217 most extensive warranties cick here for dimensions chart the product referenced on this detail page is sold be each","title":"ADC PROSPHYG 760, Newborn, Black 760N","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":640579},"price":40.41,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000B66RVO","answerTime":"2012-10-25","unixTime":1351148400.0,"question":"is thiscuff compatible with ua 767 plus monitor","answer":"yes it is that is what purchased it for","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"this durable nylon cuff is comfortable and easy to use and fits large arm sizes 11 to 17 the cuff has strong velcro hook loop fastener that is tested for up to 30 000 uses and is backed by lifetime warranty","title":"LifeSource UA-281 Blood Pressure Monitor Cuff, Large (14.2&quot; - 17.7&quot;)","salesRank":{"Electronics":6854},"price":18.95,"brand":"LifeSource"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000BJDNW2","answerTime":"2012-11-25","unixTime":1353830400.0,"question":"do the wheels lock","answer":"yes wendy the wheel locks of the wheels there are that can lock so when you assemble the wheel you might want to place the lock wheels at the feet where you want to lock it preferred my lock wheels to be diagonal from each other instead of on the same side","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"30 15 top with walnut wood grain melamine laminate with flush mounted mold edge","title":"Medline Standard Overbed Table","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":86199},"price":61.2,"brand":"Medline"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000C235Q2","answerTime":"2012-12-19","unixTime":1355904000.0,"question":"is it still has box and plastic seal around","answer":"when bought mine it was not opened it was sealed in the box with plastic","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"introduced in 2002 fragrance notes patchouli gernium amber and melon warm and inviting recommended use evening","title":"Polo Blue by Ralph Lauren for Men, After Shave , 4.2 Ounce","salesRank":{"Beauty":244903},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000C9MB74","answerTime":"2012-11-26","unixTime":1353916800.0,"question":"does it have multiple speeds","answer":"no only on off and open","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"discreet powerful waterproof massager with interchangeable soft tpr tips aa battery","title":"Berman Center Athena Waterproof Mini Massager (Packaging may vary)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":698},"price":6.09,"brand":"Berman Center"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000CEMWHI","answerTime":"2012-12-09","unixTime":1355040000.0,"question":"can use with handheld shower head","answer":"yes you should be able to use it with handheld shower head the showerbreeze attaches fits between the water source and the shower head or in your case the shower hose","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"get the showerbreeze this ingenious device flushes out loosely attached plaque and food particles trapped between teeth and under the gum line where brushing and flossing can x2019 reach attach the showerbreeze to any showerhead for easy accessibility and immediate results the unit has volume control from complete off to compete on and everything in between valve is constructed of chrome plated brass","title":"ShowerBreeze 3' Hose Oral Irrigation","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":12420},"price":24.95,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000CQEJGI","answerTime":"2012-12-15","unixTime":1355558400.0,"question":"can you list the amounts of each ingredient so can compare to what buy locally","answer":"you can find the ingredients listed on drugstore com url if the link does not work let me know and will list the ingredients for you be aware that the 98 caplet formula has half the content listed on drugstore com per caplet and thus requires that you take caplets daily the one on drugstore com is new formula that requires you to take only caplet daily","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"estroven maximum strength is clinically shown to reduce hot flashes and night sweats it contains higher level of the key black cohosh and soy isoflavones ingredients found in estroven regular strength plus additional vitamins and minerals for women health","title":"Estroven Maximum Strength - 98 Caplets","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":129411},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000E8WIAS","answerTime":"2012-12-13","unixTime":1355385600.0,"question":"are those ingredients right ordered this and mine says water stevia natural flavors vanilla extract","answer":"yes basically that is right purified water organic stevia leaf extract natural flavors vanilla extract","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"gilbert arizona based wisdom natural brands is the parentcompany of five highly respected consumer brands sweetleaf stevia wisdom of the ancients yerba mate sweet and slender natural sweetener wisdom nutrition and la merced organic yerba mate james may the founder of wisdom natural brands was involved in bringing stevia to the united states over 20 years ago the company is now the leading us manufacturer of stevia and offers full line of sweetleaf stevia products they are available in convenient single serving packets liquid powder tabs and concentrate including their best selling product sweetleaf steviaplus which was developed by james son steve together this father and son team has introduced millions of people in north america to stevia at time when producers and consumers are increasingly drawn to products that claim to be all natural low calorie and low in carbs stevia has caught the eye of health conscious consumers it has been around for centuries and is just now becoming the rage with the sugar shunning crowd in part because of the popularity of low carbohydrate high protein diets that discourage sweets stevia is nutritional supplement that adds naturally sweet taste to your current diet made from an intensely sweet extract of natural stevia leaves it has zero calories zero carbohydrates and zero glycemic index","title":"Sweet Leaf Sweet Drops Vanilla Creme Flavored Liquid Stevia, 2-Ounce Bottle","salesRank":"x","price":9.99,"brand":"SweetLeaf"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000EG7DSM","answerTime":"2012-10-17","unixTime":1350457200.0,"question":"are there packges of the count containers making it 18 containers","answer":"yes","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Glad SimplyCooking OvenWare 8x8 Baking Containers, 56 Ounces, 3 Count (Pack of 6)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":142434},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000F4S99U","answerTime":"2012-12-23","unixTime":1356249600.0,"question":"is this cuff really large cuff need large cuff for accurate reading","answer":"this is regular size cuff for regular sized adult to get an accurate blood pressure on large adult you will need to order an extra large cuff regular sized cuff will not give accurate readings on really large arm proper fit is important for an accurate reading suggest you look on another site if there are none on amazon make sure that it comes with guage included unless you already have one and stethoscope","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"the 760 series features bull contemporary black enamel 300mmhg no pin stop manometer provides day in day out dependability provides day in day out dependability bull adcufftm nylon cuff with adc 8217 proprietary size guidetm marking system prevents mis cuffing bull dip molded latex inflation bladder withstands heavy use bull chrome plated brass air release valve bull leatherette carrying case with durable nylon zipper bull assembled inspected and packaged in the from foreign components bull lifetime calibration warranty coverage two year part warranty coverage adc medical instruments and accessories have been carefully designed to meet the rigorous demands of the most discriminating healthcare professionals throughout the world adc products are manufactured from the finest materials with an uncompromising concern for quality exhaustive inspection of every item by adc factory trained quality control staff ensures strict compliance with adc standards for performance and durability and the commitment to manufacturing excellence is backed by the industry 8217 most extensive warranties cick here for dimensions chart the product referenced on this detail page is sold be each","title":"ADC PROSPHYG 760, Newborn, Black 760N","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":640616},"price":40.41,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000F4U8MQ","answerTime":"2012-12-23","unixTime":1356249600.0,"question":"is this cuff really large cuff need large cuff for accurate reading","answer":"this is regular size cuff for regular sized adult to get an accurate blood pressure on large adult you will need to order an extra large cuff regular sized cuff will not give accurate readings on really large arm proper fit is important for an accurate reading suggest you look on another site if there are none on amazon make sure that it comes with guage included unless you already have one and stethoscope","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"the prosphyg 760 series from adc is the model of choice for medical professionals who are looking for high quality at an affordable price contemporary black enamel 300mmhg no pin stop manometer provides day in day out dependability adcuff nylon cuff with adc proprietary size marking guide marking system prevents mis cuffing","title":"American Diagnostic Corporation Sphygmomanometer, Royal Blue, Adult","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":193148},"price":19.99,"brand":"American Diagnostic"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000FPE23Q","answerTime":"2012-12-01","unixTime":1354348800.0,"question":"can the heat be used independently of the massage function","answer":"yes heat can be used independantly of the other functions as well as with other massage functions","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"scholl soothing full cushion massager has motors for direct massage and intesity the independently controlled zones it has massage intensities there is handset to activate the heat feature and operate controllable zones there is an ac and auto adaper to provide comfort massage in the home office or car","title":"Dr. Scholl's DR8573 Soothing Full Cushion Massager","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":6930},"price":22.98,"brand":"Dr. Scholl&#39;s"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000FS4EPE","answerTime":"2012-12-07","unixTime":1354867200.0,"question":"hi does your product kills the norovirus am emetophobic and need something that effectively kills the virus that causes the stomach flu thank","answer":"yes viruses are deactivated by intense uv radiation as produced by the degerm inator and when used as directed please visit the manufacturer web page for this product to find chart of microorganisms and how much energy is required to render them harmless you will find this page at www dot degerminator dot com jks","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"in the news the degerminator uv sanitizer was tested in 2008 at major hospital tests were performed in patient room to locate germ colonies next few seconds of germicidal uv light from the degerminator was applied to sanitize the test areas retesting found no active germ colonies remained proving the degerminator works as advertised so don be fooled by larger wands they re all imitations of the degerminator all made overseas and none of them not one can outperform the degerminator because only the degerminator uses genuine spectroline fluorescent uv tubes recognized as the most effective and used in professional laboratory settings world wide the patented degerminator portable uv sanitizer is the second generation of this breakthrough technology it operates on aa alkaline or nickel cadmium rechargeable batteries and comes with an ac adapter for extended use the patented degerminator was the first portable uv sanitizer offered anywhere in the world and it is the only portable uv sanitizer that is made in america designed engineered and built right here in new york our competitors lamps are all mass produced overseas the degerminator will sanitize any object or surface on which germs may be threat around the home office or on the road it will sterilize toothbrushes cooking and eating utensils baby toys and nursery surfaces food preparation surfaces even glass of drinking water literally in seconds to protect yourself and your family from contracting disease or illnesses there is no faster or more effective way than by using the patented degerminator portable uv sanitizer and for those who want to avoid or limit the use of toxic chemical cleaners and disinfectants the degerminator is an excellent alternative it is the ultimate green cleaning product we say clean with soap and water disinfect with light manufacturer full year warranty and the best customer service you ever had guaranteed","title":"SpectrolineUV-5D Degerm-Inator Portable Ultraviolet Sanitizer","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":33071},"price":89.89,"brand":"Spectroline"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000FW3Z6O","answerTime":"2012-12-15","unixTime":1355558400.0,"question":"is the battery of both the watch and the chest strap replaceable by user","answer":"both are replaceable they should last two years or so","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"for fitness enthusiasts who need timing features and would like to track basic heart rate information the polar rs100 offers the needed features at an affordable price the device can help improve your fitness by making use of personal target heart rate zones and displays calories burned in an accurate easy to read format the rs100 comes complete with comfortable fabric transmitter and coded heart rate transmission to avoid cross talk ownzoneknowing the right intensity to improve your fitness can be challenge ownzone adjusts your heart rate training zone to perfectly match your body x2019 current physiological condition by using ownzone you can be sure you x2019 re training at an intensity that improves your aerobic fitness owncalowncal is the one of most accurate calorie counters on the market it calculates the number of calories expended during training session based on your weight height age gender your individual maximum heart rate hrmax and how hard you x2019 re training polar ownzone feature adjusts your heart rate training zone to perfectly match your body x2019 current physiological condition what in the box polar rs100 heart rate monitorpolar rs100 training computerrs100getting started guidefeaturesbody measurementautomatic age based target zoneaverage and maximum heart rate of each lapaverage and maximum heart rate of trainingheart rate as bpm or percentage of maxhr based target zones with visual and audible alarmhrmax age based or user set manual target zone as bpm or percentage of maxdataedit wrist unit settings with polar uplink tool and transfer them to your polar product uplink traininghearttouch button free operation of wrist unit99 lapsuser configurable displayswatchbacklightdate and weekday indicatorkeylocklow battery indicatortime of day 12 24h with alarm and snoozewater resistant to 50 meterswarrantypolar timing products include limited two year manufacturer warranty against defects in materials and workmanship about polarestablished in 1977 polar products help you understand and maximize your training the company combination of expertise in sports physiology and electronics results in an innovative product line of fitness tools for athletes of all ability levels to achieve desired results","title":"Polar RS100 Heart Rate Monitor and Stopwatch","salesRank":"x","price":86.99,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000GP5HMU","answerTime":"2012-10-16","unixTime":1350370800.0,"question":"does it help libito","answer":"didn notice difference either way with my labido but after about two weeks of using the product did notice my heart fluttering quite often so discontinued use shortly thereafter didn have anymore heart fluttering","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"nitrix is dietary supplement that is taken throughout the day to promote blood vessel dilating and muscle volumizing effects thereby supporting blood flow and enhanced muscular performance the key to the nitrix formula is the inclusion of the amino acid arginine precursor to nitric oxide high levels of nitric oxide are known to dilate the blood vessels which can have multitude of positive effects on muscular performance and appearance nitrix promotes workout performance endurance and anti fatigue additionally nitrix promotes vascularity and muscle pumps nitrix lays the groundwork for all further physique and performance improvements by taking nitrix throughout the day athletes ensure that their muscles are operating at their full potential and that they are getting the most out of the time and energy they sacrifice to training","title":"BSN Nitrix A.M. to P.M. Vaso-Muscular Volumizer, 180 Tablets","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":17879},"price":41.3,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000GP5HMU","answerTime":"2012-10-16","unixTime":1350370800.0,"question":"does nitric help libito","answer":"used this product and did not feel any such effect however have used other products with arginine and have now let me ask you question what is the difference between arginine and arginine akg","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"nitrix is dietary supplement that is taken throughout the day to promote blood vessel dilating and muscle volumizing effects thereby supporting blood flow and enhanced muscular performance the key to the nitrix formula is the inclusion of the amino acid arginine precursor to nitric oxide high levels of nitric oxide are known to dilate the blood vessels which can have multitude of positive effects on muscular performance and appearance nitrix promotes workout performance endurance and anti fatigue additionally nitrix promotes vascularity and muscle pumps nitrix lays the groundwork for all further physique and performance improvements by taking nitrix throughout the day athletes ensure that their muscles are operating at their full potential and that they are getting the most out of the time and energy they sacrifice to training","title":"BSN Nitrix A.M. to P.M. Vaso-Muscular Volumizer, 180 Tablets","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":17879},"price":41.3,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000GP0O3M","answerTime":"2012-10-16","unixTime":1350370800.0,"question":"does it help libito","answer":"didn notice difference either way with my labido but after about two weeks of using the product did notice my heart fluttering quite often so discontinued use shortly thereafter didn have anymore heart fluttering","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"nitrix is dietary supplement that is taken throughout the day to promote blood vessel dilating and muscle volumizing effects thereby supporting blood flow and enhanced muscular performance the key to the nitrix formula is the inclusion of the amino acid arginine precursor to nitric oxide high levels of nitric oxide are known to dilate the blood vessels which can have multitude of positive effects on muscular performance and appearance nitrix promotes workout performance endurance and anti fatigue additionally nitrix promotes vascularity and muscle pumps nitrix lays the groundwork for all further physique and performance improvements by taking nitrix throughout the day athletes ensure that their muscles are operating at their full potential and that they are getting the most out of the time and energy they sacrifice to training","title":"BSN Nitrix A.M. to P.M. Vaso-Muscular Volumizer, 360 Tablets","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":10310},"price":68.29,"brand":"BSN Sports"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000GP0O3M","answerTime":"2012-10-16","unixTime":1350370800.0,"question":"does nitric help libito","answer":"used this product and did not feel any such effect however have used other products with arginine and have now let me ask you question what is the difference between arginine and arginine akg","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"nitrix is dietary supplement that is taken throughout the day to promote blood vessel dilating and muscle volumizing effects thereby supporting blood flow and enhanced muscular performance the key to the nitrix formula is the inclusion of the amino acid arginine precursor to nitric oxide high levels of nitric oxide are known to dilate the blood vessels which can have multitude of positive effects on muscular performance and appearance nitrix promotes workout performance endurance and anti fatigue additionally nitrix promotes vascularity and muscle pumps nitrix lays the groundwork for all further physique and performance improvements by taking nitrix throughout the day athletes ensure that their muscles are operating at their full potential and that they are getting the most out of the time and energy they sacrifice to training","title":"BSN Nitrix A.M. to P.M. Vaso-Muscular Volumizer, 360 Tablets","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":10310},"price":68.29,"brand":"BSN Sports"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000HM9UYI","answerTime":"2012-12-17","unixTime":1355731200.0,"question":"can you use the zee wrap dispenser for aluminum foil foil is 12 inches wide","answer":"the tube has to be minumum of and inches of inside diameter and 12 inches in length on order for it to fit","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"13 plastic wrap dispenser with cutter teeth mounts under cabinet against wall or on counter includes roll of plastic wrap white boxed made in canada by jim scharf ezee wrap sold as each","title":"Jim Scharf-Ezee Wrap Dispensr 1000 Plastic Wrap Dispenser","salesRank":{"Kitchen & Dining":20463},"price":26.5,"brand":"Jim Scharf-Ezee Wrap"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000HQ0L2E","answerTime":"2012-06-04","unixTime":1338793200.0,"question":"would love to see them offer snap on combs to trim rather than shave","answer":"agree that trim combs are absolutely needed mangroomer are you listening","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"the mangroomer do it yourself electric back shaver is absolutely the best way to get rid of unwanted back hair this one of kind device features large inch blade that enables you to shave larger areas of your back with ease the mangroomer cutting edge blade design delivers extremely close and smooth results without the potential of ingrown hairs that are commonly caused by straight edge and foil shavers and with the unique patent pending design the mangroomer opens to staggering 135 degrees so you can reach all areas of your back from different angles with ease rid yourself of unsightly unwanted back hair without waxing chemicals laser or electrolysis all from the comfort and privacy of your own home why is the mangroomer right for you one time purchase with one low cost easy to use lightweight and do it yourself offers fully extendable and adjustable handle that locks into place at various lengths to reach even the most difficult middle and lower portions of the back for men of all sizes allows you to rid yourself of unwanted back hair in the privacy of your own home not some fancy or overpriced salon or spa completely painless unlike waxing chemicals laser or electrolysis folds into neat compact size for discreet storage or travel shave your back whenever you feel you need it and it is perfect for quick touch ups mangroomer vs alternate hair removal optionsbefore the mangroomer there were three hair removal options waxing chemicals and laser electrolysis waxing is an effective way to remove hair but it is incredibly painful waxing actually rips hairs right out of their follicles violently removing them from your body and since you certainly can wax your own back you ll need to make an appointment and pay someone to do apply the wax and rip it off your back with your hair chemicals are also another viable option for hair removal but it too comes with it own set of cons with chemical treatment there is chance that skin irritation and scarring may occur and similar to waxing chemical treatment must be applied by someone else chemical treatments are also notorious for noxious fumes that make for an uncomfortable and embarrassing hair loss treatment the third treatment option laser electrolysis hair removal is very expensive and similar to the other treatment options it cannot be done in the comfort and privacy of your own home it requires multiple treatments and does not stop the growth of any new hair plus it doesn even guarantee that it will stop the hair growth of treated follicles combine these embarrassing option with expensive costs and you ll see why some many people are switching to the mangroomer the mangroomer folds out to whopping 135 degrees it is breeze to reach those difficult hairy lower back areas the shaver even extends to tackle the hard to reach middle back dispelling the shaving mythdoes shaving make your hair grow back thicker darker faster according to study from the mayo clinic the answer is no in an article from mayo clinic dermatologist lawrence gibson and his colleagues the shaving myth is officially debunked shaving hair doesn make it grow back thicker it also doesn affect the color or rate of growth the color location thickness and length of hair on your body mainly depends on genetics and hormones after you shave body hair it may feel coarse or stubbly for time as it grows out during this phase body hair may be more noticeable and it may appear darker or thicker but it not the mayo clinic article also stated that you should see your doctor if you have sudden increase in facial or body hair how the mangroomer can improve your lifelook and feel clean and manicured eliminating unsightly back hair presents more refined clean image to others confidence increase your confidence knowing that you are back hair free and no one will be staring or snickering at you or get turned off by unsightly back hair romance start up that spark in your relationship or marriage by surprising your partner with smooth sexy back muscle definition shaving the hair off your back shows your muscle definition in much greater detail you ll simply look in better shape after using the mangroomer sweat keep your back shaved clean and help keep your back dry with less sweat and less chance for body odor first impressions as the saying goes you only get one chance to make first impression don let back hair ruin the image you are trying to project summer essentials when your shirt is off this summer no back hair is big plus whether you re at the beach or pool party use the mangroomer to avoid embarrassing hairy back jokes avoid embarrassing public treatment options with the mangroomer you can shave your back privately easily quickly painlessly and inexpensively by yourself in the comfort of your own home","title":"MANGROOMER Do-It-Yourself Electric Back Hair Shaver","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":4993},"price":25.99,"brand":"MANGROOMER"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000JINW3A","answerTime":"2012-11-02","unixTime":1351839600.0,"question":"do they have warranty","answer":"really don know but have used mine virtually daily for more than months without hitch some similar sets offer 90 day warranty and am well beyond that the kit is so inexpensive compared to others that didn care about warranty by the time would pay for return postage insure it and do without it for few weeks to obtain service under warranty it was really not worth it to me am considering purchasing another kit to have as back up in case mine should ever fail but so far no complaints","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"complete diagnostic set with different instrument heads all accessories and 25v power supply includes otoscope ophthalmoscope bent arm illuminator nasal speculum and tongue depressors and adapters fitted carry case am physician and have worked very hard to make improvements with every production of this kit from our manufaacturer this is not welch allyn quality yet but in my opinion it is the best of the inexpensive ent kits on the market today most of the inexpensive ophthalmoscopes on the market do not work this one actually does all can say is to purchase it along with any other brand and compare you will be glad you did","title":"ENT Diagnostic Kit - 3.25V Otoscope, Ophthalmoscope, E.N.T Diagnostic Kit","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":22600},"price":129.92,"brand":"RA Bock Diagnostics"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000KQJNNO","answerTime":"2012-11-19","unixTime":1353312000.0,"question":"does it work for 240v","answer":"don know what 240v is but it comes with it own charging base and plugs into regular outlet","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Remington WDF-5000 Smooth and Silky ladies shaver (factory refurbished)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":283630},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000KQJNNO","answerTime":"2012-11-19","unixTime":1353312000.0,"question":"is it rechargeable","answer":"yes don overcharge it limited charging will extend the life of the shaver","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Remington WDF-5000 Smooth and Silky ladies shaver (factory refurbished)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":283630},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000LQI2S0","answerTime":"2012-12-10","unixTime":1355126400.0,"question":"will it work on european current","answer":"this machine will not work on european current but if you purchase direct from the company www marpac com there are dohm ds models available for eu uk and au electrical currents","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Dohm-SS Single Speed Sound Conditioner by Marpac  (formerly known as the Sleepmate\/Sound Screen 580A)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":3212},"price":37.75,"brand":"Marpac"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000LX2MQ6","answerTime":"2012-11-06","unixTime":1352188800.0,"question":"is hte handy seat difficult to open and close","answer":"at first it was awkward as there aren really directions for what to do once you get it open there is initial stiffness but that loosened up once it was opened and from then on it was easy one thing that is mentioned on the package is that you sit on it facing the handle this gives you control and the handle is nice arm rest like it and 72 years old","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"1616c designed for people who require either walking or resting assistance perfect for individuals who suffer from asthma arthritis hip or leg surgery fibromyalgia back injury or any other physical situation that makes walking difficult provides easy mobility at minimal cost seat height 21 weight capacity 250 lbs year warranty against manufacturers defects non adjustable in height shipping carton size 36 12 10 seat dimensions","title":"Handy Seat Walking Cane","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":268110},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000M29NZY","answerTime":"2012-11-30","unixTime":1354262400.0,"question":"can you turn over the base container without all the daily strips falling out of the base container","answer":"you can turn the base container over and the daily dosage compartments will stay in place they snap in snugly all can be snapped out at once to refill as needed","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"large day weekly pill organizerthe apex large day weekly pill organizer is pill carrier designed to hold individual day week pill medication allowances the large day weekly pill organizer features highlighted raised lettering braille and 28 individual pill compartments for individuals who take medication up to times day using the large day weekly pill organizer makes it easier to understand the times and amounts of medication one is to take the use of this pill organizer helps assist those individuals who may forget the times they need to take prescribed medication doses buy your carex large day weekly pill organizer from activeforever today save when you order larger quantities save each when you order 100 pill organizerssave each when you order 200 pill organizers","title":"Large 7 Day Weekly Pill Organizer - Large 7 Day Weekly Pill Organizers - 70027PL70027PL","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":14123},"price":10.5,"brand":"Carex Health Brands"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000M2TY3U","answerTime":"2012-12-14","unixTime":1355472000.0,"question":"will this battery work on my otoscope 71050","answer":"yes it work for my 71050","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"welch allyn replacement nicad rechargeable battery orange for 71000 71000 model 72300","title":"Welch Allyn Replacement NiCad Rechargeable Battery (orange) for 71000-A \/ 71000-C - Model 72300","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":19031},"price":37.2,"brand":"Welch Allyn"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000M5NPKU","answerTime":"2012-11-15","unixTime":1352966400.0,"question":"is there any weight gain associated with this product","answer":"not that ve notice but ve always struggled with my weight took saliva test with my who told me that my adrenal glands were not functioning properly they recommended them","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"adren alls special blend of vitamins and adaptagenic herbs provides adrenal support for fatigue stress and host of other telltale signs of low adrenal function","title":"Ortho Molecular - Adren-All 120 Capsules","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":3715},"price":38.51,"brand":"Ortho Molecular Products"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000NUTUCG","answerTime":"2012-12-28","unixTime":1356681600.0,"question":"is it safe for lash extentions","answer":"don know but think you can call 281 342 3350 and ask ocusoft they have answered my questions","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"ocusoft lid scrub foam size 50 ml","title":"Ocusoft Eyelid Scrub Foaming Eyelid Cleanser - 50 Ml","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":8910},"price":10.1,"brand":"OCuSOFT"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000NW0J7E","answerTime":"2012-10-22","unixTime":1350889200.0,"question":"does it talk in spanish thanks","answer":"not that could tell it only spoke in english","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"four alarm talking watches with date announcement this handsome silver tone watch speaks the time and date has four separate alarms talking 24 hour stopwatch and optional hourly time announcement it comes with an adjustable stainless steel band 756474","title":"Men's 4 Alarm Talking Watch and Date","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":46325},"price":39.95,"brand":"MAGNIFYING AIDS"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000NWKHNA","answerTime":"2012-12-11","unixTime":1355212800.0,"question":"does this watch alarm speak the alarm","answer":"yes the watch speaks the actual time when you press the talking button and the alarm time when set when not using the alarm make sure that the bell is not showing it drains the battery when the watch stops working due to depleted battery replacing the battery is difficult and if you actually get the new battery installed you generally lose the speaking feature so the watches are pretty much disposable have had several of these watches and have had to discard them after trying to change the battery and losing the speaking feature hope this helps","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"product description x2022 announces time and date in female voice x2022 set four daily medical reminder alarms with snooze x2022 large lcd displays time and date x2022 hourly time announcement talking stopwatch x2022 uses one cr2016 lithium battery included keep your daily routine running efficiently without ever missing dose of medicine or missing an important appointment this men talking alarm medical watch lets you set up to daily talking alarms or use the talking stopwatch to time and track your activities you can see the time and day of the week displayed on the large lcd or hear it announced and set an hourly chime and time announcement features specifications announces time and date in natural sounding female voice can set four daily alarms with snooze as schedule or medication reminder large lcd displays time day of week date and year talking stopwatch with lap keep track of time spent on activities and record lap time hourly time announcement hear the time every hour on the hour can be turned off 100 year calendar date is auto programmed for the years 2000 to 2099 color black grey plastic case and band stainless steel back uses one cr2016 lithium battery included press and hold the talking button for seconds to turn on the watch this watch is equipped withn power saving mode to preserve battery life to turn off the power saving mode hold the talk button down for seconds this will activate the watch to put the watch in sleep mode once it is activated hold the talk button again for seconds and it will put it back into the sleep mode","title":"Man's Modern 4 Alarm Talking Watch , Silver and Black","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":72870},"price":16.22,"brand":"Ovo"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000NX7G24","answerTime":"2012-11-24","unixTime":1353744000.0,"question":"will this size fit childs stomach he is size 4t","answer":"it is possible that it will fit his stomach purchased these as wig caps for adults and kids as part of professional ballet production and it seems to me that some adult heads would be as wide as young child torso the material especially if cut on the thin side has great deal of give good luck","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"elastic nets","title":"Medline Elastic Net Sz 5 Stretch, 12 Inch x 25yd","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":251747},"price":13.91,"brand":"Medline"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000ODVGOM","answerTime":"2012-10-24","unixTime":1351062000.0,"question":"have kohler 10273 bn forte widespread lavatory faucet do you think your product would fit it","answer":"this product comes with many adapters that fit wide range of faucts we have two in the home and it was ez to install sometimes the adapter that it comes with you might not even use you would just attach the irrigator directly to the faucet bet one of the adapters will fit and you should have no problems but if nothing works redibreeze will send an email after purchase and you can contact them if needed for an adapter that will fit","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"this oral irrigator attaches directly to home faucets to create system for rinsing gums and promoting better dental health without tools chrome plated brass valve gloms on to existing faucets with an included adaptor if necessary the valve is equipped with switch that diverts the flow of water in the regular position water flows freely through the valve as though it were normal faucet providing running water for washing hands filling cups or hiding the sounds of telltale heart when switched on it diverts water through 24 hose that comes ready to attach to two tips that funnel the water into fine stream to clear away food and debris","title":"RediBreeze Oral Irrigator","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":10889},"price":29.95,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000PJ72I4","answerTime":"2012-12-20","unixTime":1355990400.0,"question":"is this the one with room for brushes in the top it is not opened on the pic so can tell","answer":"yes it does open on top","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Braun 4729-649 Plaque Remover Charger Tower","salesRank":{"Home &amp; Kitchen":380785},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000QB5UC6","answerTime":"2012-12-25","unixTime":1356422400.0,"question":"will this item display your heart rate as you excercise theoregon scientific wm100 scientific smartsync data logger heart rate monitor with pc downl","answer":"no just logs data you could see your pulse on your watch","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"smartsync heart rate logger records workout data from any 3khz heart rate monitor chest belt and downloads information onto pc via usb connection direct data upload to pc start time and date stamp for every session up to 99 sessions 30 hour memory storage splash proof","title":"Oregon Scientific Smartsync Data Logger Heart Rate Monitor with PC Download","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":135867},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000R72ONM","answerTime":"2012-10-22","unixTime":1350889200.0,"question":"is this the cranberry lumbar wrap the cinnamon clove eucalyptus scent","answer":"yes it is the same scent as the green have both the smell is fantastic to me pick up on the scent of cinnamon mostly","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"take journey to euphoria where relaxation and free movement await you dreamtime back in motion lumbar wrap encourages tight tense stressed muscles to relax with healing warmth or cooling touch the lumbar wrap is designed to wrap around any body part back neck knees or head and the adjustable velcro belt hold grain packs snugly in place while allowing freedom of movement","title":"DreamTime Back in Motion Lumbar Wrap, Sage Velvet","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":174894},"price":35.51,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000R70YJ8","answerTime":"2012-10-22","unixTime":1350889200.0,"question":"is this the cranberry lumbar wrap the cinnamon clove eucalyptus scent","answer":"yes it is the same scent as the green have both the smell is fantastic to me pick up on the scent of cinnamon mostly","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"take journey to euphoria where relaxation and free movement await you dreamtime back in motion lumbar wrap encourages tight tense stressed muscles to relax with healing warmth or cooling touch the lumbar wrap is designed to wrap around any body part back neck knees or head and the adjustable velcro belt hold grain packs snugly in place while allowing freedom of movement","title":"DreamTime Back in Motion Lumbar Wrap, Cranberry Velvet","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":182884},"price":9.89,"brand":"DreamTime"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000RH0JGQ","answerTime":"2012-06-07","unixTime":1339052400.0,"question":"can oxy gen2 be used on hard floors also","answer":"would not hydrogen peroxide breaks down organic compounds wood is an organic compound","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"bissell oxy gen cleaning solution fights stains with oxygen with no mixing of powder and water required this formula permanently removes stains like red wine cola and fruit juice bissell xfffd oxy gen2 can be used as pretreatment on your carpets or with color safe laundry fabrics","title":"BISSELL OXYgen BOOST Portable Machine Formula, 32 ounces, 0801A","salesRank":{"Home &amp; Kitchen":417},"price":12.83,"brand":"Bissell"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000S88ZW4","answerTime":"2012-12-13","unixTime":1355385600.0,"question":"are those ingredients right ordered this and mine says water stevia natural flavors vanilla extract","answer":"yes basically that is right purified water organic stevia leaf extract natural flavors vanilla extract","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"all natural zero calories sweetleaf liquid stevia with all natural flavors is convenient and easy to use as supplement add nutritious stevia to water tea coffee milk sparkling water protein shakes plain yogurt or anything else you can imagine zero carbohydrates zero glycemic index this statement has not been evaluated by the food and drug administration this product is not intended to diagnose treat cure or prevent any disease","title":"SweetLeaf Liquid Stevia, Lemon Drop 2 fl oz (60 ml)","salesRank":{},"price":11.37,"brand":"SweetLeaf"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000U08ZN4","answerTime":"2012-06-22","unixTime":1340348400.0,"question":"pressure sensor light always on has anyone noticed that their pressure sensor light is on anytime the troothbrush is turned on","answer":"to fix mine just had to smack it against my hand without the brush head on on all four sides few times think something may have been pressed against the sensor and causing it to stay on","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"review font family verdana helvetica neue arial serif font size 12px section head width auto margin 0px 10px 0px padding 20px background abd0e1 color 000000 border 1px dotted 212a59 caption font family verdana helvetica neue arial serif font size 10px font weight bold font style italic headline font size 15px font weight bold ul indent list style inside disc text indent 10px text align left td review font family verdana helvetica neue arial serif font size 12px","title":"Oral-B Triumph 9900 Toothbrush with Smart Guide","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":179980},"price":119.36,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000UK2W4C","answerTime":"2012-11-26","unixTime":1353916800.0,"question":"do have to turn the brush off to change modes","answer":"clean sensitive and massage modes can be adjusted on the fly go care and max care will need to have the unit turned off in order to engage","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Philips Sonicare HX6932\/10 FlexCare RS930 Rechargeable Electric Toothbrush","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":42650},"price":193.99,"brand":"Philips"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000UZEQJQ","answerTime":"2012-11-11","unixTime":1352620800.0,"question":"does it work for conair hair clipper very important need quick answer","answer":"it perfect thanks","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"wahl 10 clipper comb leaves hair fits all wahl full size clippers","title":"Wahl #10 clipper guide comb, 1&amp;1\/4.","salesRank":{"Home &amp; Kitchen":7072},"price":7.26,"brand":"Wahl"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000V0EPDC","answerTime":"2012-12-25","unixTime":1356422400.0,"question":"are they true to size","answer":"yes they are true to size had to do no adjusting or cutting to get the proper fit","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"encapsulated with two new foams our orthotic shell that has satisfied more than million consumers hypurcel foam that maintains its density and cushioning support covers the upper surface and soft eva foam coats the undersurface this exciting new product provides comfort in an orthotic not available in today market","title":"Powerstep Pinnacle Orthotic Insert PN-K (M14-14.5)","salesRank":{"Industrial & Scientific":24815},"price":32.35,"brand":"Powerstep Pinnacle"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000VGFUEE","answerTime":"2012-12-12","unixTime":1355299200.0,"question":"can the electric cord be detached from the main pad","answer":"no it is permanently attached on the bob neck wrap however the sunbeam neck wrap does have detachable cord","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"the only heating pad that relaxes the neck shoulders upper back chest other heating pads relax the neck muscles but not the muscles that go to the neck therefore you still have neck tension bob neck wrap heating pad applies gentle heat to the neck and the muscles going to the neck for more complete benefit if the chest is tight it pulls the shoulders forward which effects your posture and puts tension on the muscles bob neck wrap heating pad relaxes the chest muscles which provides benefit to the neck and upper back washable cover automatic shut off 120 minute easy to use controls helpful for people with headaches migraines wanting joint and muscle pain relief massage and relaxation this can be used with manipulation therapies replacing heat patches and wraps or electric massagers add the neck wrap heating pad as part of your health care or alternative medicine medical supplies and equipment physical therapy aids","title":"Dr. Bob's - Neck Wrap Heating Pad - 24&quot; x 23&quot;, 4 - Heat Settings, Dry \/ Moist Heat","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":8727},"price":49.95,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000X1HOH8","answerTime":"2012-12-31","unixTime":1356940800.0,"question":"have rolling trolley with base built in for pro mag lamp the receptacle size is like typical rolling caster does this have that capability","answer":"am not exactly sure what you are asking about receptacle size but do know have had the premium wheeled magnifier floor lamp for over three years and use it all the time have it set up near my chair so that when my husband watches tv almost in the dark turn mine on so can see when am crocheting which do all the time if something happens to this lamp will definitely purchase another like it with no hesitation hope this helps","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"an outstanding value in premium quality task light used in salons clinics and manufacturing plants affordable for home use weighted leg roller stand provides excellent stability 30 fixed height base with 34 flex arm gives you standing sitting positioning options plus reach over obstacles convenient power switch on lamp head dust cover protects and keeps lens clean when not in use low maintenance classic white finish on all steel construction lamp head is impact resistant abs 72 prong grounded power cord ul listed diopter magnification 25x has focal range object distance from lens of","title":"Premium Wheeled Magnifier Floor Lamp - Strong 5-Diopter Magnifcation","salesRank":"x","price":98.99,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000Z2BQ6A","answerTime":"2012-12-08","unixTime":1354953600.0,"question":"is this brand new and unopened","answer":"yes","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"peace calming is gentle fragrant blend when diffused it helps calm tensions and uplift the spirit promoting relaxation and deep sense of peace when massaged on the bottoms of the feet it can be wonderful prelude to peaceful night rest","title":"Peace &amp; Calming Essential Oil by Young Living Essential Oils - 15 ml","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":5141},"price":36.99,"brand":"Young Living"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B000Z9361G","answerTime":"2012-12-07","unixTime":1354867200.0,"question":"are these now foods lysine 500 mg vegetarian capsules or rough tablets","answer":"they are vegetarian formula but are white hard tablet but with smooth surfaces the tablet is long 16 wide and deep","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"lysine is an essential amino acid which means that it cannot be manufactured by the body xa0 it must be obtained through the diet or by supplementation xa0 lysine is one of the most well known amino acids and is an essential component of proteins","title":"NOW Foods L-Lysine 1000mg, 100 Tablets","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":1812},"price":9.29,"brand":"Now Foods"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0010EG6PI","answerTime":"2012-12-23","unixTime":1356249600.0,"question":"do they contain dairy","answer":"the label states that they do contain traces of milk and soy","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"udo x2019 choice children x2019 probiotic was formulated to meet the digestive needs of children ages 15 years it contains strains of friendly bacteria with billion viable cells per capsule at date of manufacture designed to reflect normal healthy childhood microflora it supports the development of flora in the small and large intestines udo x2019 choice children x2019 probiotic helps maintain proper digestion and strengthen the immune system use extra strength amount to relieve symptoms associated with intestinal discomfort unique company features at flora we have been manufacturing and supplying quality herbal remedies for distribution in the united states since 1988 but our roots stretch back to germany in the early 1900 where otto greither grandfather of the current owner thomas greither dedicated his life to the discovery production and distribution of natural health care products we have preserved his original dedication to perfect european herbal remedies that ensure maximum purity quality and potency product specifications 60 caps","title":"Udo's Choice Children's Blend Probiotic 60 Capsules","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":27404},"price":17.41,"brand":"Udo&#39;s Choice"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0010XNC06","answerTime":"2012-11-08","unixTime":1352361600.0,"question":"is this battery rechargeable","answer":"yes bought and charge them nightly","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"this is replacement sla battery for universal power ub1270 40800 with terminal f1 187 032 we supply only brand new factory fresh high quality batteries we guarantee the best price and 100 compatibility with your universal power ub1270 40800 model the replacement sla batteries also include minimum of one year warranty popular applications for our sla batteries are ups emergency lighting security fire and burglar alarms scooters wheelchairs medical and other","title":"12 Volt 7 Amp Hour Alarm Battery","salesRank":{},"price":10.05,"brand":"UPG"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B00125X72A","answerTime":"2012-10-17","unixTime":1350457200.0,"question":"does this product contain any wheat products","answer":"the direct answer to your question is don know there are no warnings about it being manufactured in an environment or on equipment used for milk wheat nuts etc there no 800 number on the label for me to call or to provide you don know chemical the components of wheat or wheat by products here all ingredients listed on the label active ingredient in each caplet sennosides mg inactive ingredients colloidal silicon dioxide croscarmellose sodium dicalcium phosphate magnesium stearate microcrystalline cellulose hope the information provided helps","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"indications senna gen tablets by generic senokot relieves occasional constipation generally produces bowel movement in to 12 hours stimulant laxative comfortable convenient relief in an easy to take tablet","title":"Senna-Gen Tablets by Generic Senokot - 1000 ea","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":62551},"price":15.22,"brand":"Generic Senokot"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B00126XOI6","answerTime":"2012-12-20","unixTime":1355990400.0,"question":"can this product be used with normal non rechargeable aa batteries","answer":"yes but the rechargeables seem to last longer than regular batteries","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"all the power of full size clipper in rechargeable miniature size","title":"Wahl Professional 8663 Peanut Cordless Clipper\/trimmer","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":7513},"price":39.53,"brand":"Wahl Professional"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0012TLPBQ","answerTime":"2012-12-13","unixTime":1355385600.0,"question":"do this shaver come with case","answer":"there is no travel case if that is what you are asking their is plastic cap for the top area but that is about it","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"the washable philips norelco speed xl 8240 rechargeable shaver boasts cutting technology for fast and close shave its three speed xl shaving tracks provide optimum cutting performance for accurate results while smarttouch contour following technology delivers increased comfort its antibacterial coating makes cleaning easy the speed xl comes with lithium ion battery that provides 50 minutes of power per charge for convenient and comfortable shaving experience the new philips norelco speed 8240 features 50 more shaving surface for fast close shave the new contour following system follows the contours of the face catching each hair with one stroke the shaver simply rinses clean for easy maintenance the precision cutting system features ultra thin heads with slots to shave long hairs and holes to shave the shortest stubble super lift and cut technology ensures close shave with dual blade system designed to lift hairs to cut comfortably below skin level made in holland","title":"Norelco 8240XL Men's Rotary Shaver","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":144936},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0013TMFV4","answerTime":"2012-11-26","unixTime":1353916800.0,"question":"is it possible to use inside model hq 440 because didn saw the model in descriptions","answer":"if the heads fit your hq440 don see why they won work hope this helps take are and good luck","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"hq4r electric razor heads set of three replaces norelco hq4 norelco hq4 plus 1915xl 1915xr shaver heads fits norelco electric shaver models 5812xl 5625x 5426lc 200sc 300sx 3405lc 3601x 3605x 3801xl 3805xl 3865xl 400dx 410db 4601x 4602x 4625x 4805xl 4807xl 4816xl 4817xl 4821xl 4825xl 482xl 4845xl 484xl 4865xl 486xl 4885xl 5426lc 5625x 500rl 501rl 505rl 600rx 605rx 665rx 700rl 705rl 710rl 715rl 720rl 725rl 750rl 800rx 805rx 815rx 825rx 835rx 850rx 875rx 885rx 895rx 900rx 905rx 915rx 935rx 945rx 950rx 955rx 965rx 968rx 985rx hp1318 hp1319 hp1327d hp1328e hp1328s hp1337c hp1601 hp1602 hp1604 hp1605 hp1606 hp1608 please note this is replacement part and is not manufactured by norelco","title":"HQ4R Electric Shaver Heads. Replaces Norelco HQ4 Heads.","salesRank":{"Beauty":22802},"price":13.33,"brand":"Shaver Aid"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B00157BZ9C","answerTime":"2012-11-14","unixTime":1352880000.0,"question":"does it have alcohol list all ingredients please","answer":"just read the ingredients and it does not contain alcohol hope this is helpful","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"breath spray","title":"CLOSYS breath spray mint flavor .25fl oz","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":82914},"price":1.0,"brand":"CloSYS"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0015QSU9Q","answerTime":"2012-10-23","unixTime":1350975600.0,"question":"the ingredients aren listed wish the label was posted is there any sweetener in the natural flavor including stevia","answer":"the 100 natural whey protein powder does not contain any artificial sweeteners this is only the natural flavor version the flavored ones do contain sweeteners though not sure which ones you can see copy of the nutritional label at this site url here is list of the ingredients whey protein isolate natural french vanilla flavor soy lecithin xanthan gum contains milk and soy there is no yeast wheat gluten preservatives artificial color artificial flavor or artificial sweeteners","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"biochem ultimate lo carb whey contains 100 pure ultra filtered micro filtered uf mf whey protein isolate the finest quality and most easily assimilated whey protein isolate available with 99 undenatured whey peptides the naturally occurring biologically active components of whey protein isolate are beneficial to athletes bodybuilders and to others who wish to incorporate additional high quality protein into their diets ultimate lo carb whey is fat and lactose free with gram of carbohydrate per serving and mixes instantly with the liquid of your choice","title":"Biochem Ultimate 100 % Whey protein, Natural, 24.6-Ounce Can","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":5587},"price":31.58,"brand":"Bio Chem"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0015TEP5Q","answerTime":"2012-11-10","unixTime":1352534400.0,"question":"is this pack of as appears in the photo","answer":"yes it is five pack","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"medica quikclot 1st response advanced clotting sponge rapidly stops moderate to severe arterial and venous bleeding and is easily applied by even non medical personnel quikclot 1st response has been re engineered to remain cooler on contact it has greatly reduced exothermic reaction with maximum temperatures in vivo typically at 105 degrees quikclot 1st response is easy to use just rip open packet pack the self contained sponge into the wound and the bleeding stops rapidly for larger wounds use more than one sponge the sponges will conform to the shape of the wound quikclot 1st response is easily removed in the hospital setting","title":"Z-medica Quikclot 1st Response Advanced Clotting Sponge","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":76900},"price":45.98,"brand":"Z-medica"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0016BVON4","answerTime":"2012-12-28","unixTime":1356681600.0,"question":"do you have the extra large size available","answer":"purchased pair for my mom as gift the size chart they used ran smaller than they way they fit we returned them for larger size we never received the larger size or refund be careful","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"foot warmers provide soothing warmth and pain relief to tired aching feet the cozy fleece material is filled with premium natural grains that conform to the shape of the foot when heated the grains slowly and evenly release therapeutic warmth ideal for arthritis tendonitis stiffness chronic cold feet and sore or aching feet heat quickly in the microwave reusable one pair fits men or women color black caution not to be worn while walking not suitable for persons with diabetes or anyone with decreased sensitivity swelling of the feet or ankles or decreased circulation persons with these conditions should consult physician before use should not be worn in place of regular slippers the foot warmers are not designed for outdoor use","title":"Therall Therapeutic Foot Warmers, Medium","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":160661},"price":39.96,"brand":"Florida Orthopedics"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0016BXSE2","answerTime":"2012-12-28","unixTime":1356681600.0,"question":"do you have the extra large size available","answer":"purchased pair for my mom as gift the size chart they used ran smaller than they way they fit we returned them for larger size we never received the larger size or refund be careful","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"foot warmers provide soothing warmth and pain relief to tired aching feet the cozy fleece material is filled with premium natural grains that conform to the shape of the foot when heated the grains slowly and evenly release therapeutic warmth ideal for arthritis tendonitis stiffness chronic cold feet and sore or aching feet heat quickly in the microwave reusable one pair fits men or women color black note for health and hygenic reasons this item is not returnable once worn caution not to be worn while walking not suitable for persons with diabetes or anyone with decreased sensitivity swelling of the feet or ankles or decreased circulation persons with these conditions should consult physician before use should not be worn in place of regular slippers the foot warmers are not designed for outdoor use","title":"Therall Therapeutic Foot Warmers, Large","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":324847},"price":39.96,"brand":"Florida Orthopedics"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0016BXSDS","answerTime":"2012-12-28","unixTime":1356681600.0,"question":"do you have the extra large size available","answer":"purchased pair for my mom as gift the size chart they used ran smaller than they way they fit we returned them for larger size we never received the larger size or refund be careful","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"foot warmers provide soothing warmth and pain relief to tired aching feet the cozy fleece material is filled with premium natural grains that conform to the shape of the foot when heated the grains slowly and evenly release therapeutic warmth ideal for arthritis tendonitis stiffness chronic cold feet and sore or aching feet heat quickly in the microwave reusable one pair fits men or women color black caution not to be worn while walking not suitable for persons with diabetes or anyone with decreased sensitivity swelling of the feet or ankles or decreased circulation persons with these conditions should consult physician before use should not be worn in place of regular slippers the foot warmers are not designed for outdoor use","title":"Therall Foot Warmers - Small - 53-4254","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":458673},"price":38.97,"brand":"Therall"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0017QSZY4","answerTime":"2012-12-26","unixTime":1356508800.0,"question":"are parker razors made in the usa","answer":"no they are made in india","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"the parker 22r is classic the razor is all metal genuine brass frame with nickel chrome plating this razor provides an incredibly smooth shave when coupled with the shark blades the parker 22r weighs ounces and is perfect for both new and expert wet shavers we believe this razor will rival any on the market for shave closeness and comfort even those costing much more the head on this razor has been designed to angle the blade for smooth and comfortably shave don let the beautiful looks of this razor fool you it is meant to shave with and it will reward you with barbershop shave every time","title":"Parker 22R - Long Handle Butterfly Open Double Edge Safety Razor &amp; 5 Shark Super Chrome Blades","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":16295},"price":28.77,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0019LTH3U","answerTime":"2012-12-30","unixTime":1356854400.0,"question":"does this product contain any maltodextrin","answer":"no it doesn contain maltodextrin ing are stevia extract water vegetable glycerin and natural flavors","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"nu naturals alcohol free stevia pure liquid oz 59mlnunaturals alcohol free stevia pure liquid is for individuals that are sensitive to alcohol here is product especially for you for everyone else the unique sweet taste that the glycerine imparts makes this favorite of many nunaturals stevia pure liquid","title":"NuNaturals Nustevia Alcohol Free Stevia Glass Bottle Liquid, 2-Ounce","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":4730},"price":11.78,"brand":"Nunaturals"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0019ZEVZU","answerTime":"2012-12-11","unixTime":1355212800.0,"question":"can the battery be changed the charge on mine doesn last long at all","answer":"no the battery cannot be replaced the battery should last years so if you have new unit and the battery is not holding charge would call philips directly also make sure you leave it on the charger long enough to get fully charged 24 hrs or so philips states that hr charge will give you enough power for minute brush","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Philips Sonicare HX6711\/02 HealthyWhite 710 Rechargeable Electric Toothbrush","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":6566},"price":87.0,"brand":"Philips"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001ADL1SG","answerTime":"2012-12-12","unixTime":1355299200.0,"question":"does the mist go in whole room even when this is on full power the mist goes up only around feet high and then seems like falling down","answer":"have no scientific way to measure how far and wide the mist disperses but it feels like it is making the air in the room more moist guessing that the further away from the device the less moist the air becomes will tell you that chose the cranes have base on very positive tests conducted by consumer reports","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"the modern simplistic design of the crane drop shape cool mist humidifier makes it tasteful addition to any room in your home finalist in the 2011 international housewares design awards the crane drop shape cool mist humidifier provides up to 24 hours of moisture on medium setting suitable for rooms up to 250 square feet in size this compact unit is energy efficient and uses ultrasonic technology to add soothing moisture to dry air crane drop humidifier provides relief for cough and cold nasal congestion and dry itchy skin available in an array of stylish colors the drop humidifier is an ideal combination of form and function and makes great gift for any occasion this humidifier does not require filter to operate cool mist white and blue drop shape humidifierat glance turns cold tap water into cool calming mistsoothes cold symptoms dry skin and chapped lipsruns whisper quiet up to 24 hours on medium settingreleases up to gallons of moisture per dayfeatures colorful modern designdoes not require filterphysician recommendedstylish energy efficient design uses ultrasonic technology to add soothing moisture to dry air view larger efficient humidifier with contemporary designthe crane drop shape cool mist humidifier runs up to 24 hours and puts out up to gallons of moisture to soothe cold cough and flu symptoms 360 degree nozzle lets you direct the cool mist while variable output control located on the front of the unit makes for easy operation this humidifier is energy efficient using less power than standard light bulb to run helps relieve the discomforts of nasal congestion dry itchy skin chapped lips and dry throat view larger benefits of this crane humidifierhumidifiers are an ideal choice for relieving the discomforts of nasal congestion dry itchy skin chapped lips and dry throat the moisture that humidifiers add to dry air helps alleviate common nuisances brought on by winter heating such as static electricity peeling wallpaper and cracks in paint and furniture many physicians recommend the use of humidifier to help relieve congestion from the common cold and flu as an alternative to over the counter cough and cold medicine the drop shape cool mist humidifier was finalist in the 2011 international housewares design awards thanks to its fun contemporary design and whisper quiet operation it is discreet enough to be left out when company visits straightforward whisper quiet operationnot only are crane humidifiers stylish but they are also easy to use and include built in auto shut off feature that engages when the water tank is empty to ensure safety the whisper quiet operation helps provide for good night sleep for everyone operating the crane drop shape ultrasonic cool mist humidifier requires only few easy steps simply remove the water tank from the unit unscrew the tank cap and fill the water tank under water faucet securely replace the tank cap making sure the rubber cap seal is in place and place the water tank back onto the unit place the humidifier on an elevated surface and set it to medium output setting for comfortable room humidification important tipsif you have lot of minerals in your tap water it is recommended to use distilled water filtered water or crane demineralization filter hs 3161 place humidifier on an elevated surface and not on carpet towel or sensitive wood furniture cleaning and storagefrequently cleaning your humidifier is very important crane recommends emptying the water in the basin daily making sure you pour away from the fan air outlet disinfect the water basin and tank weekly by using white vinegar and fresh water solution let sit for 30 minutes then rinse for convenience the crane descaler solution hs 1933 is also available it is important to disinfect and dry completely before storage what in the box crane white and blue drop shape cool mist humidifier and operation manual warranty cool mist drop shape humidifiersgreenorangepinkwhitewhite and blue","title":"Crane Drop Shape Ultrasonic Cool Mist Humidifier with 2.3 Gallon output per day","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":16259},"price":47.44,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001ATATX8","answerTime":"2012-12-16","unixTime":1355644800.0,"question":"does this product have beeswax in the ingredients","answer":"the other ingredients listed on the label are dicalcium phosphate vegetable cellulose vegetable magnesium stearate silica it says contains milk and soy free of wheat yeast and gluten without artificial preservatives favors or colors hope this helps","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"vitamin also known as menaquinone supports normal blood clotting and activates enzymes responsible for bone formation trademarked variety of vitamin called menaq7 great way to get your daily value of this vital nutrient easy to swallow softgels","title":"Solgar Natural Vitamin K2 (MK-7) Vegetable Capsules, 100 Mcg, 50 Count","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":23070},"price":10.7,"brand":"Solgar"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001AXVF28","answerTime":"2012-12-12","unixTime":1355299200.0,"question":"is this test strip compatible with onetouch ultramini meter","answer":"ve been using them with my one touch ultra mini works great to test my diabetic fur baby","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"for blood glucose testing with one touch ultra and one touch ultrasmart brand meters and induo systems","title":"One Touch Ultra Blue Mail Order Test Strips, 50 CT","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":1008},"price":26.5,"brand":"One Touch Ultra"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001AYZMWQ","answerTime":"2012-10-22","unixTime":1350889200.0,"question":"the photo shows blades but the descriptions says need blade for wood stove is this the correct item","answer":"that the right fan description but the wrong picture the number of blades is not requrement for wood stove different models are set for different heat ranges gs is for gas stoves it won handle the extremes wood stove is capable of read the descriptions two blades will pump 100 fpm three blades will handle 150 fpm you want blades this isn house fan don expect lot of speed you will feel the heat flow across the top of the stove and rise into the room to the side of the stove have blade 802 it is delightful addition to the top of my 1976 vermont castings defiant it also great conversation starter","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"heat powered wood stove fan creates its own electricity from the heat of the stove increase your comfort the ecofan allows the warm heated air to circulate throughout your room one year warranty for customer service please call 800 567 3556","title":"Caframo Limited 812AM-KBX Ecofan Airmax, Nickel Blade","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":82102},"price":128.99,"brand":"Caframo Limited"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001BLEHDI","answerTime":"2012-12-22","unixTime":1356163200.0,"question":"will it fit through 23 inch doorway","answer":"no the widest part are the back wheels they are 23 wide","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"this fab bantex rollator serves as walker chair and wheelchair solution for those who can walk but then may need assistance lightweight wheelchair solution weighs 22 lbs weight capacity is 250 lbs seat is 14 13 nearly 18 between bars includes good size basket too","title":"Bantex Transport Rollator Walker\/Chair\/Wheelchair -- 3-in-1 solution","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":15656},"price":130.64,"brand":"American Bantex"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001C3Z4M8","answerTime":"2012-10-29","unixTime":1351494000.0,"question":"is this pressurized some lighter fluids are not pressurized and won work","answer":"no it not pressurized it just the fluid in can with nozzle and you squeeze it to get it to come out","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"oz can of lighter fluid","title":"Single Can, Zippo Fluid, 4 oz can","salesRank":"x","price":4.25,"brand":"Zippo"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001EPQ3H4","answerTime":"2012-08-26","unixTime":1345964400.0,"question":"20pr 2pack does that mean 40 total","answer":"no 20 pair per package 40 plugs per package 80 plugs total","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"the ultimate softness series was launched as the original hearos ear plug in 1992 today eighteen years later this ear plug is used by millions of people who want to sleep better protect their hearing and reduce noise","title":"Hearos Ultimate Softness Series Foam Earplugs, 20-Pair","salesRank":{"Home &amp; Kitchen":446},"price":5.86,"brand":"Hearos"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001ET6ZTG","answerTime":"2012-12-14","unixTime":1355472000.0,"question":"is the manufacturer out of business","answer":"no","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"ezo holds upper and lower dentures tight with vacuum grip when dentures are new they grip with natural vacuum over time gums can recede and dentures can slip ezo denture cushions help recreate the natural vacuum that keeps dentures in place made of pure cotton flannel paraffin wax and corn oil ezo denture cushions add extra cushioning with no bad taste or odor and last up to 24 hours","title":"Ezo Denture Cushions, Lower Heavy, 15 Cushions (Pack of 6)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":8359},"price":20.07,"brand":"Ezo"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001F0PVMG","answerTime":"2012-12-13","unixTime":1355385600.0,"question":"is there way of displaying the heart rate with calories and time this was feature of another polar watch","answer":"hi believe calories are only displayed after you have finished training during training time is displayed as well as heart rate heart rate is on linear scale with designations for fat burning levels and maximum heart rate level also use cardio trainer app on my smartphone when run or bike outside and use my fitness pal app as well after workouts to track things like calories exercise hope that helps kathy","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"stay within your ideal training and intensity range while jogging or working out with the polar ft40 women heart rate monitor watch the ft40 works by first checking your daily condition and then guiding you to the ideal training intensity for your age and fitness level knowing your heart rate not only helps you reach your personal fitness goal but also improves your physical condition in general as it vitally important to train at the appropriate intensity level if you exercise too hard you may quit before you reach the real benefit but if you work out too leisurely you ll struggle to lose weight at all the ft40 helps overcome these problems by encouraging you to map out complete fitness routine the ft40 is packed with innovative training features to help you toward your exercise goals first off the watch displays heart rate info in several ways including as percentage of your maximum heart rate as beats per minute and within graphical target zone indicator the watch also offers visual and audible alarm for when you exceed or dip below your target zone great way to stay motivated while on the track and users will love the energypointer zonepointer and polar owncal modes the energypointer determines the point at which your training no longer just burns fat but also improves your overall fitness level an ideal feature for high performance runners the zonepointer meanwhile is an audible and visual feature on the display of your ft40 that shows you where your current heart rate sits within your target heart rate zone finally the polar owncal mode shows your energy expenditure during one exercise session as well as your accumulated kilocalories during several exercise sessions you can also set daily and weekly exercise goals in terms of calorie expenditure helping you achieve both short term and long term goals other features include built in fitness test that measures your aerobic fitness at rest in just five minutes zonelock mode that lets you activate target zone in the midst of training with the press of button an owncode mode that prevents crosstalk from other heart rate monitors nearby recording mode that tracks your average and maximum heart rate calorie expenditure and total exercise time and then puts it in an exercise file with 50 total files water resistance to 30 meters 12 24 hour clock with day week indicator built in backlight an alarm with snooze low battery indicator and polar flowlink connection for transferring data between the ft40 and computer sporting an attractive green housing the watch carries two year warranty manufacturer warrantythe original purchaser of this heart rate monitor is backed by limited warranty that states that this product that the product will be free from defects in material or workmanship for two years from the date of purchase about polarthe first ekg accurate wireless heart rate monitor was invented by polar back in 1977 as training tool for the finnish national cross country ski team the concept of intensity training by heart rate swept the athletic world in the eighties by the 1990s individuals were looking to heart rate monitors not only for performance training needs but also for achieving everyday fitness goals today the same concept of heart rate training is being used by world class athletes as well as everyday people trying to lose weight polar is the leading brand among consumers coaches and personal trainers worldwide and the company is committed to not only producing the best products but also being the leading educator on the benefits of heart rate based exercise","title":"Polar FT40 Women's Heart Rate Monitor Watch (Green)","salesRank":"x","price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001F0RBT2","answerTime":"2012-11-05","unixTime":1352102400.0,"question":"do get two boxes 24 pads total 48 or two boxes total 24 pads thank you","answer":"two boxes of 24 each total 48","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Swiffer WetJet Spray Mop Floor Cleaner Pad Refills, 24-Count (Pack of 2) (Packaging May Vary)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":10932},"price":27.55,"brand":"Swiffer"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001FWXKMM","answerTime":"2012-04-12","unixTime":1334214000.0,"question":"is this irt 4520 made in germany","answer":"fyi purchased three orders one is made in mexico and another two are made in german cannot guarantee that you will get german made","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"designed to give you some peace of mind when your child comes down with fever the braun thermoscan ear thermometer with exactemp technology has all the features you could ever want in thermometer used by more doctors offices than any other infrared thermometer brand the thermoscan features pre warmed tip that improves accuracy unique guidance system that ensures precise results and infrared technology that takes your child temperature in seconds view largerview largerproduct specificationsmodel irt 4520categoryinfrareddimensions9 06 85 54 inchescolorblue whitewarranty60 daysrelated productlf 40 ear thermometer lens filtersear thermometers deliver most precise readingsif you are the parent of young child you probably know all too well that the average baby gets seven fevers year clinical studies prove that ear thermometers reflect changes in core body temperature faster than oral thermometers and more accurately than rectal or temple measurements rectal temperatures lag behind changes in core body temperature so they are not always reliable indicator temple and underarm measurements take skin temperatures not core body temperatures so they can be influenced by external factors such as sweating or drafts likewise oral temperatures can be influenced by external factors such as drinking eating and breathing the eardrum however shares its blood supply with the temperature control center of the brain so changes in body temperature are reflected sooner and more accurately in the ear than in other places pre warmed tip and guidance system ensure accuracy every timewhen you use the braun thermoscan you can be sure you ll receive professional level results every time unlike other ear thermometers braun thermoscan exactemp features patented pre warmed tip this feature minimizes the cooling effect on the ear canal that can result from using room temperature tips meaning you get the most accurate results possible additionally the thermoscan unique exactemp technology with guidance system confirms with light and beep when you have taken proper measurement an exactemp light flashes during the measuring process and signals when the probe has not been placed correctly in the ear canal the light shines continuously once the temperature has been taken and beep signals that you have an accurate reading and when you have to regularly monitor your baby temperature the thermoscan memory function facilitates by keeping track of the development of the temperature storing up to eight different results infra red technology and flexible tip make measurement fast and gentlethe braun thermoscan is the perfect thermometer for parents who have fussy children the thermoscan measures the infrared heat generated by the eardrum and surrounding tissue giving an accurate temperature in just few seconds with such fast measurement time and with small soft flexible tip the thermoscan is as gentle as can be in fact the thermoscan is so gentle and fast you can take your baby temperature while he or she is sleeping without worrying about an unscheduled wake up lens filters improve accuracy and safetyto ensure the accuracy of every temperature reading new clean lens filter should be used for each measurement lens filters protect the tip from scratches as well as from impurities such as earwax which might adversely affect the accuracy furthermore exchanging the lens filter before every temperature reading virtually eliminates the risk of spreading germs from one person to the next for ease of use lens filter detector makes sure that lens filter always is in place and lens filter ejector makes removing used lens filters as easy as can be about braun award winning design quality and innovationbraun strives to fulfill consumer needs by creating products that have innovative features and benefits high quality performance and durability and ergonomic distinctive and aesthetic design braun products consistently achieve outstanding ratings tests conducted by independent consumer organizations and international awards and exhibitions document the reputation of the company and its products what in the boxbraun thermoscan ear thermometer with exactemp technology protective case lens filters and batteries","title":"Braun Thermoscan Ear Thermometer with ExacTemp Technology, IRT4520USSM","salesRank":"x","price":39.88,"brand":"Braun"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001FXUTUM","answerTime":"2012-12-30","unixTime":1356854400.0,"question":"is this suitable for guys have fine facial hairs and thinking that those mirco hair trimmer would work instead of this rem","answer":"as long as the hair isn coarse think it would work just fine it doesn seem to do well with very coarse or very fine hairs","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"hair removal","title":"R.E.M. Spring Facial Hair Remover","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":4776},"price":19.95,"brand":"R.E.M. Spring"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001FXUTUM","answerTime":"2012-10-18","unixTime":1350543600.0,"question":"does this work on coarse hair am african american and need something that will get rid of short thick facial hair thanks","answer":"yes it works on any type of hair promise have friends here that use it and they are of mexican spanish and dark skin types","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"hair removal","title":"R.E.M. Spring Facial Hair Remover","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":4776},"price":19.95,"brand":"R.E.M. Spring"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001G0G4N0","answerTime":"2012-12-22","unixTime":1356163200.0,"question":"can this be used to place persosn in car","answer":"if you have smooth surface you can move it but the wheels are small so they can go over too much of bump it would work to put person in the car if the car isn too low you just unhook the sling with the person sitting on it then just hook it back up when you are ready to take them back into the house","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"the features of the 9805p include padded swivel bar and push handle 450 pound weight capacity durable construction and 360 degrees patient rotation without side to side sway lightweight construction and easy disassembly allow quick transport and setup and with its slim design the hydraulic lift is versatile enough to use for any and all patient moves indispensable to patients and caregivers alike the 9805p offers safety comfort and stability most important it offers peace of mind which makes it valuable asset to your health care facility this item is painted not chrome 20 64 range allows for patient to be picked up from lying position on floor elongated handle design serves broad range of operator heights and offers improved handling ability offset mast and boom style provide better lift path maximizing full travel range pump handle can rotate from side to side for convenience of attendant six point swivel bar attachment easily adapts to all sling styles and positionsbase length 46 75 back width open 42 25 closed 22 caster options front rear overall height maximum at sling hookup 64 minimum at slinghookup 20 base height clearance product weight 68 lbs product weight capacity 450 lbs","title":"Invacare 9805P Personal Hydraulic Patient Body Lift","salesRank":{"Industrial & Scientific":4295},"price":374.99,"brand":"Invacare"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001G7QG72","answerTime":"2012-10-23","unixTime":1350975600.0,"question":"is this fragile glass","answer":"no it plastic bottle","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"babies will the love the 100 percent natural orange flavor of these delicious vitamin drops clinical studies show that dha an important nutrient found in breast milk helps support normal brain and eye development in infants twinlab infant care drops provide this important nutrient for your baby as well as 100 of the daily value of ten recommended vitamins the highest quality vitamin sources including 100 natural vitamin are used","title":"Twinlab Infant Care Multi Vitamin Drops With DHA, 1 2\/3 Fl Oz. (50 ml), (Pack of 3)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":5467},"price":16.3,"brand":"Twinlab"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001G7QVWC","answerTime":"2012-11-04","unixTime":1352012400.0,"question":"this posting says that get packs am guessing bottles of 60 tablets for 16 30 is that correct","answer":"yes","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"dietary supplement hplc verified balances dhea levels helps enhance energy anti aging precursor no yeast wheat corn milk egg soy glutens artificial colors added sugar starch or preservatives these statements have not been evaluated by the","title":"Natrol DHEA 50mg, 60 Tablets (Pack of 3)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":2638},"price":16.5,"brand":"Natrol"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001GAOHPM","answerTime":"2012-10-11","unixTime":1349938800.0,"question":"according to the listing do understand that the quantity of this package is two pairs is this correct","answer":"yes received pair have one line drying while wear the other","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"imak arthritis gloves were designed by an orthopedic surgeon and help relieve aches pains and stiffness associated with arthritis of the hands the unique design provides mild compression for warmth and helps increase circulation and promote healing the open fingertips allow full freedom to feel touch and grip all day ideal for arthritis hand swelling and cold hands they may also help with neuropathy and poor circulation use in the office around the house or for knitting gardening crafts and hobbies the gloves are also comfortable for use during the night arthritis gloves have received the ease of use commendation from the arthritis foundation arthritis gloves are made of soft breathable cotton lycra and can be hand washed in cold water and air dried","title":"Imak  Arthritis Gloves Small  One Pair, (Pack of 2)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":70511},"price":32.95,"brand":"Brownmed"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001GE7PPC","answerTime":"2012-10-12","unixTime":1350025200.0,"question":"do these come in plain sunglasses no strength","answer":"yes they do not sure if you can get them on amazon but you can find them on the web just search clic sunglasses","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"these clic sun reading glasses win by nose instead of hooking over the ears these unique sun readers wrap around the head and close in front with neodymium magnet when theyre not needed they rest around the neck courtesy of the built in head strap lost readers are thing of the past available in powers from 125 to 300","title":"Reading Sunglasses by Clic - Tortoise Magnetic Sunglasses, 2.50","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":390892},"price":30.95,"brand":"CliC"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001GQ3GF8","answerTime":"2012-11-04","unixTime":1352012400.0,"question":"can it work in europe mean in 220 volt","answer":"yes definitely the charger can take anything from 100 to 240 volts the plug looks like so you might need an adopter if your outlet shape is different for example shape","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"introducing the wahl deluxe self cut 18 piece do it yourself haircut kit the clipper is rechargeable for cord or cordless use the clipper has four position rotating head for easy accurate self cutting easily rotates for comfortable use on either left or right side the kit contains complete set of guide combs which aid in achieving professional looking results the kit comes with soft side case for convenient storage","title":"Wahl Deluxe Self Cut Do It Yourself Haircut Kit, 18 Pieces","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":84758},"price":39.94,"brand":"Wahl"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001JHUUSK","answerTime":"2012-11-05","unixTime":1352102400.0,"question":"does it have magnesium in it","answer":"citracal maximum does not have magnesium in it if you want magnesium then you have to buy citracal plus magnesium","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"regular exercise and healthy diet with enough calcium helps teen and young adult white and asian women maintain good bone health and may reduce their high risk of osteoporosis later in life adequate calcium intake is important but daily intakes above about 2000 mg are not likely to provide any additional benefit","title":"Citracal Calcium Citrate and D3  240-Count","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":31897},"price":18.2,"brand":"Citracal"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001KXZ808","answerTime":"2012-11-25","unixTime":1353830400.0,"question":"does the weight stay lit up little while after stepping off the scale wear bifocals and need to step back in order to read the numbers","answer":"your weight will stay on the display for about seconds after you step off","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"new features 2014 version eatsmart step on technology allows you to simply step on the scale and get your weights no more tapping to activate the scale increased capacity to 400 pounds with the same precision and repeatability that makes our products great overview the eatsmart bathroom scale is the ideal way to track your weight loss quickly and easily simply step on and in seconds you ll have an accurate readout to the nearest lbs on the eatsmart oversized accubright lcd display with eatsmart proprietary new step on technology there is no more tapping to turn the scale on the lcd display also contains cool blue backlight allowing for easy viewing even in the most low light areas of the bathroom or home industry leading design and accuracy the eatsmart digital bathroom scale is also not only easy to use but also extremely accurate engineered to the highest precision standards the four high gauge eatsmart precision sensors ensure that you will get an accurate measurement every time down to the nearest lbs kg just read our reviews additionally the slim tempered glass design fits perfectly into any surroundings and large non slip platform safely allows weights to 400 lbs what included along with your eatsmart digital scale you also receive our easy to read instruction guide and aaa batteries everything you need to weigh yourself right away along with your scale you will also receive free eatsmart body tape measure measure any body part waist biceps thigh calf chest quickly and easily to track progress eatsmart guarantee100 eatsmart guaranteed product satisfaction","title":"EatSmart Precision Digital Bathroom Scale w\/ Extra Large Lighted Display, 400 lb. Capacity and &quot;Step-On&quot; Technology [2014 VERSION] - 10,000+ Reviews EatSmart Guaranteed Accurate","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":32},"price":39.5,"brand":"EatSmart"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001R82OMG","answerTime":"2012-12-14","unixTime":1355472000.0,"question":"can you string lanyard through this product","answer":"no there are no holes in it for stringing through instead we do zip tie around the middle where the intersects and attach our lanyard through that our son won wear anything around his neck so we have clippy not sure the real term on which the lanyard it more closely resembles that curly telephone cord is affixed and the lanyard through the zip tie onto the chewy ll try to take pic and post it to the user photos feature","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"chew stixx when used properly provide safe and bacteria free alternative for children who chew on shirts pencils fingers or almost anything due to the alternating textures of this product it is an excellent chewable hand fidget for children craving sensory input and the input received from destructive oral motor grinding the textures of this product were designed by therapists to simulate the ever changing textures of food therefore assisting with children who have sensory issues when certain textures are placed in their mouth chew stixx is an oral motor device and not toy use of this product should be supervised by an adult or therapist at all times product is extremely durable but should be replaced at first sign of wear chew noted as most durable chew based on in house studies and test as compared to other oral motor device in same class","title":"CHEW STIXX ORAL CHEW (MOST DURABLE ORAL MOTOR CHEW WE SELL*)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":10812},"price":7.99,"brand":"CHEW STIXX"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B001U0OFDC","answerTime":"2012-12-28","unixTime":1356681600.0,"question":"can you set your own minimum heart rate as well as the max","answer":"did not see minimum in settings","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"polar is committed to customer satisfaction review the ft7user manualfor more information you can find additional support and information about this product at polar com us en ft7 by email at customer service usa polar com and by phone at 800 227 1314","title":"Polar FT7 Heart Rate Monitor Watch","salesRank":{"Sports &amp; Outdoors":120},"price":69.89,"brand":"Polar"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0021AFWXC","answerTime":"2012-12-04","unixTime":1354608000.0,"question":"is this product safe for bikini area ve heard some nasty things about it","answer":"it perfect ve been using it for months believe use it for the whoooole area the first time not gonna lie will be rather painful but 100 worth it after that the hairs grow back here and there alot thinner and hardly even feel it anymore now always smooth and ready to go recommendation soak in nice warm bubble bath first and then use lotion right after also the redness irritation from having your hair yanked out by its roots usually only lasts around 24 hours after few uses that also gets less noticable nothing nearly as bad as the horrible irritation get from constantly shaving the area definitely buy this absolutely love it best one ve ever used","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Panasonic ES-WD51-P Ladies Wet\/Dry Epilator","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":30330},"price":125.0,"brand":"Panasonic"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0024S00VA","answerTime":"2012-11-29","unixTime":1354176000.0,"question":"is this machine and electric one","answer":"no it hand crank","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"top matic cigarette making machine allows fast and efficient cigarette to be made with your favorite rolling tobacco and filtered tube lever action injection with an adjustable switch to allow 100mm kings and regular filtered tubes to be used includes year limited warranty","title":"New Top-O-Matic Cigarette Rolling Machine","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":34777},"price":43.98,"brand":"Lighter USA"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B00266PFI8","answerTime":"2012-11-15","unixTime":1352966400.0,"question":"is this in roll on bottle","answer":"no dap it on scarf and wear it around my neck when have cold it helps clear up my stuffy nose don think would like roll on because it can get contaminated","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"tiger balm liniment fl oz pack of","title":"TIGER BALM LINIMENT, 2 fl. oz (Pack of 2)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":19995},"price":11.9,"brand":"Tiger Balm"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0026RSZGG","answerTime":"2012-11-26","unixTime":1353916800.0,"question":"is there list of ingredients and their amounts","answer":"there is not list on here but if you go to url it has list there these are excellent vitamins","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"megafood is in the business of improving lives by staying true to the intention of food megafood is pioneer in the natural products industry being the first company to make vitamins from scratch with farm fresh whole foods as leading natural brand they have been an industry innovator by being the only supplement company to manufacture their own foodstate nutrientsand sourcing fresh and local foods from family owned farms since 1973 the company has produced some of the most effective and award winning supplements megafood has received the non gmo project verified seal from the non gmo project the non gmo project is third party certification program that assures product has been produced according to consensus based best practices for gmo genetically modified organism avoidance recommended by andrew weil","title":"MegaFood Women Over 40 One Daily Tablets, 90 Count","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":10879},"price":47.97,"brand":"MegaFood"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0027LSEPS","answerTime":"2012-11-21","unixTime":1353484800.0,"question":"started using this oral device weeks ago but every time use it got all wet my face gets wet does this normal","answer":"no it not normal put the jet tip the part that squirts into your mouth before you turn on the irrigator and turn the irrigator off before you take out the jet tip bend over the sink and let your mouth hang open as you work the jet tip from tooth to tooth you can watch the yukky stuff that was stuck between your teeth and under your gums falling out as you use the irrigator this way to clean your mouth it nice knowing that stuff isn there any more and you ll find you still get stuff out of your mouth with the irrigator even after brushing and flossing","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Panasonic Oral Irrigator EW-DJ10-A","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":997},"price":36.36,"brand":"Panasonic"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0029XLGAO","answerTime":"2012-11-05","unixTime":1352102400.0,"question":"is there any thc in this product","answer":"from nutiva com hemp faq are hemp foods legal to import buy and consume in the united states yes the case hia dea established that hemp foods are exempt from control in the controlled substances act an excellent overview of the case can be found on the vote hemp web site on their dea hemp food rules page the ninth circuit court of appeals opinion invalidating dea final rules can be downloaded here if recently consumed hemp foods could fail drug test if the only source of the psychoactive thc in your body is from hemp foods produced from canadian grown hemp seeds and eaten in reasonable quantities it is virtually impossible to fail drug test by ingesting hemp foods due to the fact that thc levels in our products are barely measurable the testpledge program is voluntary commitment by the north american hemp food industry to limit thc concentrations to levels where they cannot result in positive drug tests nutiva joined the testpledge program in 2001 nutiva hemp food products meet canadian government and testpledge standards for hemp foods we recommend that you read the testpledge answers page first if you need more technical information please download and read the study summary evaluating interference of thc in hemp food products with employee drug testing which was prepared by gero leson env and petra pless please click here to download pdf file 21k 10 17 2007 here is an mail we received about nutiva organic hemp protein powder and drug testing from department of defense employee work for the department of defense and was finally selected for random urinalysis after 18 years wasn the least bit worried until that night when went home to fix fruit shake in which use your hemp protein powder as took it out of the refrigerator it suddenly occurred to me that it has very small amount of thc in it having been drug alcohol abuse officer in the air force years ago understood the potential implications including the fact that thc is detectable far longer than many drugs of abuse called nutiva the next day and was told that because you can ever know what other behaviors customer may be engaging in you cannot say for certain that your products could not cause positive urinalysis for thc however was assured that it was highly unlikely by itself especially the protein powder because of the way it processed lower oil content than some other products promised to provide you with feedback either way my test turned out my understanding is that the department of defense uses state of the art testing passed despite using your hemp protein powder multiple times every week for months know it no guarantee but it may relieve others who are not using illegal substances but who may be using your products and become concerned about drug testing thanks","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Organic Hemp Protein 50% by Nutiva","salesRank":"x","price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002A6MCHQ","answerTime":"2012-11-02","unixTime":1351839600.0,"question":"this looks like it comes with 50 cartridges is that true","answer":"my amazon buying record shows purchased this item in june 2010 at that time it was an offer for 50 twin ii plus razor blades with lubricating strip for gillette trac trac ii razor by personna that was the title for this listing back then but the title has changed although the photo has not now the title says you get the pivot kind and it does not say you get 50 paid 23 88 back in 2010 just checked my amazon records online that means the item that is being sold and reviewed has changed over the years something that is constant problem on amazon and needs to be handled by amazon but apparently is still problem so would say without doubt as of today you will not get packs of 10 regular twin plus blades as shown in the photo you will get one pack of 10 pivot blades if you want to buy personna at decent price regular or pivot about for 10 cartridges as of today the only place can find them is alice url it would help if everyone who is interested in this product sent feedback to amazon about the incorrect photo and the constant changing of the item description and what you get this is problem when the item changes but the old reviews are attached to the changed item very misleading and is huge problem to easily send feedback to amazon please scroll down to the very bottom of the product page and you ll see the feedback links one for the image one for general feedback tell them the product image is incorrect if it still is when you read this and tell them they need to address the problem of incorrect and misleading product titles product titles changing being different than what was first reviewed and sellers not shipping what is described","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Personna Twin Pivot Plus 10 Cartridegs","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":182760},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002BR7HO2","answerTime":"2012-11-05","unixTime":1352102400.0,"question":"are there any difference between the products in 90 tablets and those in 60 tablets","answer":"well to what see the 90 that purchased came in blister packets not bottle so if you are interested in freshness the 90 count looks like it would be better choice same price per count and you save by not having to buy as often also shipping","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"nadh natural coenzyme derived from vitamin niacin is essential for basic metabolism respiration the breakdown of sugars and fats and the production of atp the primary energy molecule in our cells nadh supplies atp energy to the brain nerves muscles heart and all other organs in order to function nadh sublingual is great for traveling jet lag studying workouts athletic performance or whenever natural boost of energy is needed","title":"Source Naturals NADH 5mg, 90 Tablets","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":19130},"price":37.92,"brand":"Source Naturals"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002C7KAQI","answerTime":"2012-12-27","unixTime":1356595200.0,"question":"can cross bar be installed on these poles","answer":"ve added cross bars that we use as handrails using chain link fence parts big","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"guardian safe pole the guardian safe pole provides sure grip anywhere you grab it safe pole is made of heavy duty durable steel with special white coating that looks and feels good floor to ceiling pole safely assists with standing sitting climbing stairs or transferring no tools required for installation screw mechanism with padded bracket fits securely without marring surface white powder coated heavy gauge steel is attractive and durable height adjusts from product weight 14 lbs product height shipping dimensions box 25 21 25 shipping dimensions box 75 91 75 product weight capacity 275 lbs shipping weight 18 lbs diameter base plate","title":"Guardian Safe-T-Pole - Floor to Ceiling - Assists in Standing","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":33247},"price":84.95,"brand":"Posey"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002CQUF00","answerTime":"2012-12-22","unixTime":1356163200.0,"question":"does this product contain quercetin","answer":"yes quercetin dihydrate 100mg","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"look young naturallyreserveage organics resveratrol vcaps are meant to trigger the sirt longevity gene these caps improve your cardiovascular function and provide phytonutrients to your body the organic grapes present in the vcaps can help you reverse the signs of aging and look young triggers sirt longevity geneoptimizes potency levelmade with certified organic ingredientsmade in francethese vcaps can provide essential vitamins and nutrients to your body that are required for healthy growth just for you diet conscious men womena closer look reserveage organics resveratrol vcaps are made with the finest organic grapes to provide phytonutrients to your body the ingredients are of good quality fresh and pure dietary concerns contains no alcohol consult your dietary practitioner before using this product it should not be used during pregnancy nursing or while taking medications usage take capsule everyday fda disclaimer these statements have not been evaluated by the fda this product is not intended to diagnose treat cure or prevent any disease","title":"ReserveAge Resveratrol 250 MG, 60 Vegetarian Capsules","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":6364},"price":29.74,"brand":"Reserveage"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002CVTVVY","answerTime":"2012-12-22","unixTime":1356163200.0,"question":"are any of the rechargeab stations wall mountable","answer":"no it not wall mountable the toothbrush needs to stand vertically to be recharged now if you can figure out how to keep the toothbrush on the stand by all means mount it anywhere","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Philips Sonicare HX6972\/30 Flexcare Plus Rechargeable Electric Toothbrush","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":12287},"price":145.97,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002KFM9LQ","answerTime":"2012-11-19","unixTime":1353312000.0,"question":"is it water solueble","answer":"no it isn ve tried another brand that liquid and is water soluble didn see any difference in my energy level but there could have been other benefits wasn aware of it was considerably more expensive for sure","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"coq10 is powerful antioxidant that is necessary nutrient for cell function in the body and has been shown to have numerous health benefits in clinical research co 10 concentrations decrease as we age the heart is especially prone to reduction in coq 10 supplementing with this important hearth health antioxidant may help support healthy aging co q10 delivers important antioxidants and nutrients that help maintain healthy cardiovascular system and healthy blood pressure levels already within normal range statins reduce the natural production of coq10 statin induced coq10 deficiency is preventable with supplemental coq10 coq10 is not intended to serve as replacement for statin therapy nor should you discontinue taking any prescribed medications while supplementing with coq10 these statements have not been evaluated by the food and drug administration this product is not intended to diagnose treat cure or prevent any disease","title":"Kirkland CoQ10 Coenzyme 300 mg - 75 Softgels","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":34800},"price":17.9,"brand":"Kirkland Signature"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002LSI3J4","answerTime":"2012-10-25","unixTime":1351148400.0,"question":"can you use in car","answer":"not while driving but do not know why passenger would not be able to you need good ac to dc converter though","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"the sharper image shiatsu massage pillow with soothing heat option is great for use on back neck or shoulders spot shiatsu targets the pain for massage relief while the soothing heat helps ease stiffness and tension while kneading away muscle tension pain and fatigue featuring deep kneading shiatsu massage heads with invigorating vibration massage this versatile design allows for multiple massage positions and target locations the pillow is made with ultra soft fabric for the ultimate comfort and has conveniently attached remote control with special side storage pocket","title":"The Sharper Image MSG-P110 Neck, Back and Shoulders Shiatsu Massager Pillow, Black","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":96610},"price":51.51,"brand":"The Sharper Image"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002MZQ22G","answerTime":"2012-10-12","unixTime":1350025200.0,"question":"do these come in plain sunglasses no strength","answer":"yes they do not sure if you can get them on amazon but you can find them on the web just search clic sunglasses","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"new impulse xxl reading glasses clics clic clic eyewear has unique one piece design that lets them hang around your neck when not in use and when you put them on they just click together the patented magnet that holds them in place at the bridge of your nose keeps your clics in place during just about any activity clic readers can even be fitted with your own prescription from the boardroom to the boat from the warehouse to the slopes get pair of clics to wear in the sun there pair of clics for every occasion we also carry many other colors and styles of other models see our other listings for other choices clic reading glasses just hang in style around your neck these unique clic reading glasses are perfect for all","title":"CliC Magnetic Closure Reading Glasses XXL with Adjustable Headband Black 2.00","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":138739},"price":32.95,"brand":"Impulse Clics"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002MZU0RY","answerTime":"2012-10-12","unixTime":1350025200.0,"question":"do these come in plain sunglasses no strength","answer":"yes they do not sure if you can get them on amazon but you can find them on the web just search clic sunglasses","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"new impulse 25 xxl blk reading glasses clics clic clic eyewear has unique one piece design that lets them hang around your neck when not in use and when you put them on they just click together the patented magnet that holds them in place at the bridge of your nose keeps your clics in place during just about any activity clic readers can even be fitted with your own prescription from the boardroom to the boat from the warehouse to the slopes get pair of clics to wear in the sun there pair of clics for every occasion we carry magnifications from 25 to we carry colors of blue red clear brown black classic tortoise and crystal smoke we also carry many other colors and styles of other models see our other listings for other choices clic reading glasses just hang in style around your neck these unique clic reading glasses are perfect for all","title":"CliC Magnetic Closure Reading Glasses XXL with Adjustable Headband Black 1.25","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":55924},"price":32.95,"brand":"CliC"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002N6P02C","answerTime":"2012-10-22","unixTime":1350889200.0,"question":"will this item work on glass","answer":"would say if the glass was smooth then yes used them on paneling type board in the shower don ask that had tile effect and they would stay for time but eventually they would fall if reattached before my shower or re enforced they were good hold used on regular plastic shower wall and they held until removed when moved","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"you will receive pack of safe er grip bath and shower handle 17 inches about mommy helper safe er grip bath and shower handle get handle on bathroom safety with this bathtub and shower handle the 17 safe er grip balance assist bar for tub and shower from mhi allows you to enter wet and slippery tub or shower safely and with confidence the safe er grip assists your balance while entering or exiting the tub or shower full body weight is not to be applied to product this easy to install grip gives both parent and child steady confidence in and around the tub","title":"Safe-er Grip Bath &amp; Shower Handle, 17-Inches (Pack of 2)","salesRank":{"Industrial & Scientific":379},"price":26.26,"brand":"Mommy&#39;s Helper"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002RWZ5KO","answerTime":"2012-11-03","unixTime":1351926000.0,"question":"are they vegetarian","answer":"yes they are 100 vegetarian per the product labelling they are free of eggs shellfish even wheat milk peanuts etc","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Yummi Bears Yummi Bears Daily Multi 15 Pkt","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":736232},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002TSHGIU","answerTime":"2012-10-23","unixTime":1350975600.0,"question":"can you disable the alarm and just have it set to flash lights mom doesnt need loud alarm just help in taking medicine at the right time","answer":"yes the alarm can be shut off to be honest do not remember flashing lights my mother in law does not live in our area we turned over the dispensers to company which refills them and brings them to her when she visited we sure did hear the alarm there are different alarm to chose from and of course the selection no alarm have just ordered third dispenser for just in case the price in the us is great if bought it over here it would cost almost 200 usd highly recommend the dispenser hope this helps best lisa","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"6948181200014 features medication reminder and automated pill dispenser in one ideal for in home care and caregiver facilities 28 medication departments enable dispenser to be used for up to doses of medication per day tamper proof locking key system helps prevent over medication easy to program removable scheduling rings allow you to set medication alarms for or times day alerts at specified times with of tones and blinking red light helps ensure medication compliance for elderly alzheimer patients and the mentally or visually impaired reduces the need for personnel to distribute medication great for organizing nutritional supplements or recommending nutritional supplement plans low battery alert includes requires aa batteries included dimensions overall dimensions","title":"Med-e-lert Automatic Pill Dispenser 28 Day 7 Day 4 Times - CLEAR Lid","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":15702},"price":79.95,"brand":"Med-E-Alert"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002VI840M","answerTime":"2012-10-11","unixTime":1349938800.0,"question":"would this work with queen size bed","answer":"the one ordered is for single person or twin size it could be put on queen size frame it is not as big as queen size bed hope that helps","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"genesis deluxe inch alternating pressure and low air loss mattress system pump","title":"Genesis Deluxe 8-inch Alternating Pressure and Low Air Loss Mattress System &amp; Pump","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":250625},"price":339.95,"brand":"Genesis"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002XUL2HA","answerTime":"2012-11-03","unixTime":1351926000.0,"question":"are they vegetarian","answer":"yes they are 100 vegetarian per the product labelling they are free of eggs shellfish even wheat milk peanuts etc","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"yummi bears organics multi vitamin and mineral is the best vitamin for your child 8217 overall health its 16 essential vitamins and minerals contain the proper amount of nutrients which are important for your child 8217 growth and development our multi vitamin and mineral is specially formulated for your child so that it is allergen free gluten free casein free has no artificial colors or flavors and does not contain gelatin which makes it perfect for those who enjoy vegetarian lifestyle","title":"Yummi Bears Organics Multi-Vitamin, Gummy Vitamins for Children, 90-Count Bottle","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":1978},"price":16.59,"brand":"Yummi Bears Organics"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002Y27K6O","answerTime":"2012-12-30","unixTime":1356854400.0,"question":"is nature bounty value size milk thistle 250mg 200 gelatin capsules gluten free","answer":"yes it is it seems to avoid good many problems and specifically states gluten free on the packaging have several bounty products like","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"milk thistle 250 mg200 capsulesmilk thistle 250 mgthe exceptional benefits of milk thistle are due to powerful antioxidant properties which help to promote overall health and well being capsules may be swallowed or opened and prepared as tea nature bounty milk thistle capsules feature milk thistle which supports liver health by helping to rejuvenate liver cells milk thistlemilk thistle is concentrated herb with beneficial antioxidant properties that contribute to overall health and well being nature bounty milk thistle supplements can be used to help maintain healthy liver function herbsnatural herb supplements are used to assist the body fight against various health conditions as well as to promote general well being the use of herbal supplements along with healthy diet is beneficial to living healthy lifestyle nature bounty herbs come in variety of formulations and all products are fully assayed for potency purity and freshness circulatory healthcirculatory health is important for both men and women of all ages and activity levels taking nature bounty circulatory health supplements can help maintain healthy circulation and blood flow for overall cardiovascular wellness nature bounty quality you can count onhealth conscious people have trusted nature bounty for decades our dedication to quality consistency and scientific research has resulted in vitamins and nutritional supplements of unrivaled excellence by combining the latest breakthroughs in nutritional science with the finest ingredients nature bounty is proud to provide you with supplements of unsurpassed quality and value nature bounty supplements are overseen by scientists manufacturing specialists and quality experts each one dedicated to maintaining the highest quality standards as part of commitment to quality nature bounty only uses ingredients from suppliers that meet stringent quality assurance standards as well as gmp food quality standards every nature bounty product is subjected to numerous quality tests and assays throughout the manufacturing process to verify purity and full potency what in the boxnature bounty milk thistle 250 mg 200 capsules these statements have not been evaluated by the food and drug administration this product is not intended to diagnose treat cure or prevent any disease","title":"Nature's Bounty Value Size Milk Thistle 250mg, 200 Gelatin Capsules","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":1131},"price":11.99,"brand":"Nature&#39;s Bounty"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002YM3NOM","answerTime":"2012-12-26","unixTime":1356508800.0,"question":"is the height adjustable","answer":"yes it is adjustable should work over most toilets or as bedside commode very convenient the elongated seat is hard to find","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"","title":"TFI 3 in 1 Elongated Universal Steel Commode","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":66798},"price":113.01,"brand":"TFI Healthcare"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002YMK7SW","answerTime":"2012-12-22","unixTime":1356163200.0,"question":"will these leg rests fit the invacare 9000sl","answer":"yes it does if you download the order form from invacare here url you will see the part posted 9153637788 as an option just make sure the pin spacing is about inch older chairs had spacing of about inches if they made 9000sl this way years ago then it wont fit","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"hemi hanger pin spacing approx fits invacare wheelchairs tracer iv tracer ex2 tracer sx5 sx5 recliner 9000 xt measure distance between hanger pins part number t94hc does not come with heel loops","title":"Invacare Corporation Wheelchair Hemi Elevating Legrest, Composite Foot Plates, WITHOUT HEEL LOOPS","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":214023},"price":67.95,"brand":"Invacare"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B002YMIEB4","answerTime":"2012-11-20","unixTime":1353398400.0,"question":"is this actually the jra model not seeing jr model","answer":"it is model 6300 jra upc 016167630028","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"invacare 6300 jra walklite walker this junior size walker folds up like regular walker for easey transport and storage the 6300 jra folds so flat you can set behind the seat of an automobile this walklite tm walker revolutionized the world of walkers by addressing the needs of consumers at an affordable price the new walklites will continue to feature all the benefits of the original walklite comfortable flip up seat durable front fixed wheels rear spring loaded sureglide tm brakes lightweight aluminum frame with flexible backrest and ergonomic dual paddle folding mechanisms comes with sure glide brakes on rear legs and caster wheels in front","title":"Invacare Junior WalkLite Walker - 6300 JR","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":60438},"price":53.2,"brand":"Invacare"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B003092M9U","answerTime":"2012-12-27","unixTime":1356595200.0,"question":"is this the same charger as re7 40 searched for that for my panasonic es8243 razer and it came up with this","answer":"yes this is the one","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"this wes7058k7658 is genuine new panasonic adapter","title":"Panasonic WES7058K7658 Shaver Charging Adapter Cord","salesRank":{"Camera &amp; Photo":1375},"price":22.76,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0030T1NFO","answerTime":"2012-12-26","unixTime":1356508800.0,"question":"can use my duracell charger for these amazon basics aa batteries","answer":"yes have recharged them in both duracell and energizer charger","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"amazonbasics aa mimh rechargeable batteries are great for use in your household devices such as digital cameras toys remote controls flashlights and portable audio players the batteries are pre charged and ready to use right out of the pack","title":"AmazonBasics AA NiMH Precharged Rechargeable Batteries-8-Pack, 2000 mAh (Discontinued by Manufacturer)","salesRank":{},"price":12.99,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0031ZI88M","answerTime":"2012-12-28","unixTime":1356681600.0,"question":"can you set your own minimum heart rate as well as the max","answer":"did not see minimum in settings","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"FT7-M Men's Heart Rate Monitor Watch","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":296},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0036RMBB0","answerTime":"2012-10-12","unixTime":1350025200.0,"question":"do these come in plain sunglasses no strength","answer":"yes they do not sure if you can get them on amazon but you can find them on the web just search clic sunglasses","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"new impulse 75 xxl blk reading glasses clics clic clic eyewear has unique one piece design that lets them hang around your neck when not in use and when you put them on they just click together the patented magnet that holds them in place at the bridge of your nose keeps your clics in place during just about any activity clic readers can even be fitted with your own prescription from the boardroom to the boat from the warehouse to the slopes get pair of clics to wear in the sun there pair of clics for every occasion we carry magnifications from 25 to we carry colors of blue red clear brown black classic tortoise and crystal smoke we also carry many other colors and styles of other models see our other listings for other choices clic reading glasses just hang in style around your neck these unique clic reading glasses are perfect for all","title":"CliC Magnetic Closure Reading Glasses XXL with Adjustable Headband Black 1.75","salesRank":"x","price":32.95,"brand":"Impulse Clics"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0039EJ6P4","answerTime":"2012-11-02","unixTime":1351839600.0,"question":"does it come with the charger","answer":"yep","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"with its ergonomic design ocean offers intense spot pleasures with added clitoral or anal stimulation simultaneously neptune would be proud","title":"Fun Factory Click 'n Charge Ocean Vibe, Baby Rose","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":121676},"price":69.99,"brand":"Fun Factory"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B003DRD3PG","answerTime":"2012-12-02","unixTime":1354435200.0,"question":"do these calcium gummies have any kind of fish fish oil in them","answer":"not that can see they do however contain gelatin","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"vitafusion calcium 500 mg chewable gummy vitamins for adults 100 ct","title":"Vitafusion Calcium, Gummy Vitamins For Adults, 500 mg, 100-Count","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":1529},"price":11.98,"brand":"Vitafusion"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B003DZBYDQ","answerTime":"2012-12-31","unixTime":1356940800.0,"question":"will nubax work for short female feet tall","answer":"yes it will take some adjusting to get the relationship between the shoulders and the hip bar properly set and it will work for shorter people","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"jinv7000 features new generation of traction providing gentle but strong and effective traction to the spine no hanging upside down no pressure on ankles and knees holds the spine in completely neutral position patent protected fda approved dimensions dimensions 22 31 17","title":"Nubax Trio Back Traction","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":178814},"price":299.0,"brand":"Bad back store"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B003ECUX26","answerTime":"2012-12-09","unixTime":1355040000.0,"question":"can you sleep on it","answer":"sleep on it every night although the manufacturer says not to fall asleep with it on and it shuts itself off you will not feel any discomfort from it","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"controlled moist heat for temporary pain relief associated with muscles strains and sprains joint pain and inflammation temporarily eases back pain caused by overexertion stress and strain does not require water produces its own moisture using humidity in the air easy to read lcd controls allow user to set and monitor treatment temperature and time lock out feature guards against unintended touching of the controls during treatment includes heating pad fleece cover and instruction manual one year warranty 14 27 note for health and hygiene reasons heating pads are not returnable once used","title":"Moist Heating Pad Digital Electric 14&quot;x27&quot;","salesRank":{"Industrial & Scientific":3120},"price":59.99,"brand":"Reliamed"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B003I2ZPFC","answerTime":"2012-09-27","unixTime":1348729200.0,"question":"would the batteries work well for headset would the aaa rechargeable batteries850mah gp pre charged work as well","answer":"gp 2700 sounds like aa cell make sure you are looking for the correct size pre charged nimh cells operate just as well as regular nimh in heavy drain appliance but the runtime may be shorter due to lower capacity 2200mah instead of 2700mah in light drain appliances or those that are used once in while pre charge cells have the advantage that you don need to recharge them as frequently","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"AAA Rechargeable Batteries 800MAH GP Pre-Charged (8-pk.)SALE !!","salesRank":{},"price":13.45,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B003II4D2C","answerTime":"2012-11-24","unixTime":1353744000.0,"question":"does this product remove facial hair specifically from the upper lip","answer":"yes slightly painful but it does work","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"the emjoi divine is terrific hair remover with 36 tweezer action discs to ensure rapid non irritating and virtually painless hair removal from the root with its patented glide technology and massaging finger attachment removing hair has never been easier or more comfortable the emjoi divine removes hair as short as 5mm from the upper lip chin legs bikini line and underarms leaving skin silky smooth for up to weeks it features antimicrobial protection against damaging bacteria by silver ion technology the emjoi divine is battery operated and portable so you can use it anywhere 36 tweezer discs remove more hair in less time with less pain patented skin glide technology lifts up and removes hair by gliding the tweezer discs over the skin with less irritation patented hair guide channels flat and short hairs into hair removal discs massaging finger function minimizes pain during epilation contoured design helps keep the skin taut and minimizes pulling and discomfort built in lifetime antimicrobial protection against damaging bacteria by silver ion technology gentle enough to remove delicate facial hair on the upper lip and chin great for removing hair on the legs bikini line and underarms ergonomically designed handle is easy to hold and maneuver enjoy smooth skin for up to weeks dual speed control battery operated aaa and portable","title":"Emjoi Divine Hair Remover, White\/Pink","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":14798},"price":29.99,"brand":"Emjoi"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B003SQD4PQ","answerTime":"2012-12-08","unixTime":1354953600.0,"question":"can use this spray on natural fiber rug like jute","answer":"was told you can use any anything try small spot and let sit for 24 hours to check color fastness this stuff is awesome spray all my furniture and rugs no complaints","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"vectra gives you the ability to maintain that luxurious new look of all your fabrics and floor coverings while it is recommended for use on all your new furnishings vectra works well on older items that are freshly cleaned with slightly less dramatic results it prevents dirt from penetrating the fiber on molecular level reducing friction and the accelerated wear of your fabrics which increases its life and durability simply spray vectra onto your household items and experience years of quality protection no more hassles over scheduling fabric protection and wondering who can get the job done vectra is not waterproofer however it is moisture inhibitor and eliminates water stains","title":"Vectra Furniture, Carpet, Fabric and Wall Coverings Protector Spray, 32 Oz.","salesRank":{"Home &amp; Kitchen":29181},"price":29.99,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B003SQJ6D0","answerTime":"2012-11-14","unixTime":1352880000.0,"question":"does this watch come with the heart rate strap that is pictured","answer":"yes the small size strap was included in my package","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"makes exercise motivating funfor the first step into heart rate based training shows heart rate on large and easy to read display helps improve your fitness with manual heart rate target zone displays summary of your latest workout simple one button start and coded heart rate transmission to avoid cross talk safely exercise within your target zone records average and maximum heart rate","title":"Polar FT1 Heart Rate Monitor (SMALL)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":49687},"price":41.29,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B003UTMWYU","answerTime":"2012-11-02","unixTime":1351839600.0,"question":"does the item come with everything pictured","answer":"it does it great buy ve owned this for about months now","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"this massage table is not only great bargain during this sluggish economy but also comes complete with all functional components the frame is made of birch to ensure professional strength with weight limit of 450lb this table is easy to fold and unfold and comes with free carry case the upholstery is comprised of three inch thick high density small cell foam padding and oil water proof pu leather not cheap pvc used by others","title":"77&quot; L 3&quot; Pad Pink PU Reiki Portable Massage Table","salesRank":{"Home &amp; Kitchen":521291},"price":85.88,"brand":"BestMassage"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B003V58A5S","answerTime":"2012-12-17","unixTime":1355731200.0,"question":"does the inhaler come with the salt","answer":"yes it comes with some salt that will last you for at least year even for frequent use made mistake thinking it did not and ordered whole pack of salt that don think ll be using for at least two years","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"squip himalayan salt air inhaler few minutes of regular daily use can ease breathing benefit the respiratory system and thin mucus and ease expectoration","title":"Squip Squip-Himalayan Salt Air Inhaler, 7.75 Ounce","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":18623},"price":14.5,"brand":"SQUIP"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B003VDWDUS","answerTime":"2012-12-03","unixTime":1354521600.0,"question":"would this work with 2012 equinox","answer":"think it would work for almost any truck or van as long as you have the right hitch we are very happy with our purchase my husband can remove it easily when we aren going to be using it for while it is very stable even on the highway doing 65 mph","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"this mobility carrier has everything you need for loading and hauling your expensive mobility device the wheelchair and scooter carrier features an integrated ramp which fold up and out into different positions the first position keeps the ramp folded flat to the carrier surface and held down with spring pull pin the folded flat position is to keep the ramp self stored and secured when the carrier is folded up the second ramp position allows the ramp to stand up straight when mobility device is on the carrier the ramp is held vertically in place with spring pull pin the last position is the ramp unfolded this position allows for scooters or power wheelchairs to be pushed or driven up the ramp","title":"Wheelchair Scooter Mobility Carrier Medical Rack Ramp","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":131869},"price":182.0,"brand":"SCOOTER MOBILITY CARRIER"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B003VMEIMK","answerTime":"2012-12-31","unixTime":1356940800.0,"question":"the outside of my tub is straight but the inside of the tub has an angle to it does the inside of the tub where this connects have to be straight","answer":"hiya hmmm think that would depend on how steep of an angle the clamps on this are straight so if you re really depending on this for full weight support be hesitant to put it on unless the angle were slight lt 10 20","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"the michael graves rotating tub rail from drive medical makes it easy getting in and out of the tub at any angle the handle postion can be rotated in 45 degree increments oersize handle has soft grip which provides additional comfort easy tool free assembly makes it easy to secure to tub fits tubs to no sharp edges make bathing safer and more comfortable modern sleek design is able to fit into any decor limited lifetime warranty","title":"Drive Medical Michael Graves Rotating Tub Rail","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":307843},"price":70.82,"brand":"Drive Medical"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B003XX4Y12","answerTime":"2012-11-09","unixTime":1352448000.0,"question":"do these syringes come with caps caps are shown in the product photo but not mentioned in the description","answer":"yes they come with caps","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"monoject oral syr 3ml clear","title":"Kendall Monoject Oral Syr 3ml Clear - Box of 100 - KND8881903002KND8881903002_bx","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":25002},"price":15.1,"brand":"Kendall"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B003ZPKJCG","answerTime":"2012-10-23","unixTime":1350975600.0,"question":"are the pastic black paper plate holders microwave safe","answer":"ve used the white plate holders in the microwave for maybe minutes without issue assume the black holders are made of the same plastic as the white holders","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"unit pack of plate holders","title":"Plastic 9&quot; Paper Plate Holders in White Maryland Plastics, 4 plate holders per unit","salesRank":{"Kitchen & Dining":3080},"price":6.07,"brand":"Maryland Plastics"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B00408PKPS","answerTime":"2012-10-22","unixTime":1350889200.0,"question":"are these latex free","answer":"don believe that they have latex ve looked on the inside tag and it says cotton and spandex however would contact the seller some of that tag is worn off","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"graduated gradient compression design 100 pressure at ankle and compression lessens gradually up to calf 70 and thigh 40 design perfectly fit your leg comfortable reinforced toes and heels relief for tired aching legs and prevent thrombosis high elastic mciro fiber are delicate soft velvety stronger and do not rub at heels to make them sore 20 30 mmhg therapeutic support color black size large by us advanced healthcare great deal save with us","title":"BriteLeafs Opaque Compression Stocking Pantyhose Therapeutic 20-30 mmHg Large, Black - Firm Support Gradient Compression, Professional Grade","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":27654},"price":25.99,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0041HSAO6","answerTime":"2012-10-12","unixTime":1350025200.0,"question":"do these come in plain sunglasses no strength","answer":"yes they do not sure if you can get them on amazon but you can find them on the web just search clic sunglasses","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"impulse 50 xxl dark tortoise reading glasses clics clic eyewear has unique one piece design that lets them hang around your neck when not in use and when you put them on they just click together the patented magnet that holds them in place at the bridge of your nose keeps your clics in place during just about any activity clic readers can even be fitted with your own prescription from the boardroom to the boat from the warehouse to the slopes get pair of clics to wear in the sun there pair of clics for every occasion we carry magnifications from 25 to we carry colors of blue red clear brown black classic tortoise and crystal smoke we also carry many other colors and styles of other models see our other listings for other choices clic reading glasses just hang in style around your neck these unique clic reading glasses are perfect for all","title":"CliC Magnetic Closure Reading Glasses XXL with Adjustable Headband Tortoise 2.50","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":90439},"price":32.95,"brand":"Impulse Clics"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0044F7KS2","answerTime":"2012-12-03","unixTime":1354521600.0,"question":"is this okay to use on fiberglass tub","answer":"don see why you wouldn be able to there isn anything really abrasive on the cloth that could damage the fiberglass","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"mr clean magic reach all in one bathroom cleaning tool kit is new versatile cleaning system to easily clean tough bathroom jobs flexible shaped head cleans curved surfaces and corners kit includes magic reach mop wet mopping pads and dry scrubbing pads","title":"Mr. Clean 443865 Magic Reach All in One Bathroom Cleaning Tool Starter Kit","salesRank":{"Home &amp; Kitchen":22750},"price":19.93,"brand":"Mr Clean"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0045F54MK","answerTime":"2012-05-16","unixTime":1337151600.0,"question":"does only natural ultimate african mango extract contain caffeine","answer":"you will have to look for caffeine free most contain green tea or even hoodia which is lot of caffeine","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"only natural ultimate african mango is unique formula combining 300 mg of african mango seed extract and 200 mg of the highest quality green tea extract african mango seed is harvested in west africa where the natives have traditionally used this beneficia natural substance for its many health benefits green tea extracts contains egcgs plyphenols and antioxidants that support healthy weight loss helps maintain normal cholesterol levels assists with weight loss supports health blood sugar","title":"Only Natural Ultimate African Mango, 60-Count","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":17207},"price":8.6,"brand":"Ony Natural"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0047528HM","answerTime":"2012-12-26","unixTime":1356508800.0,"question":"will it harm septic tank","answer":"nope have septic and checked this too on the bottle it says septic safe ll post picture in second","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"lemi shine removes the toughest spots film from dishes and glassware while keeping your dishwasher sparkling clean","title":"Lemi Shine Original (12 oz)","salesRank":{"Home &amp; Kitchen":28470},"price":8.25,"brand":"Lemi Shine"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004CHSLW6","answerTime":"2012-10-24","unixTime":1351062000.0,"question":"does this machine have an input for headphones","answer":"yes there is headphone jack on the lower right hand side of the machine had to look because have never used it use the machine every night and have been very happy with it also it looks very good and is well built","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"sound sleep from adaptive sound technologies is designed to provide the most realistic natural sound environment possible to help people relax and sleep better at night each device includes ultra high quality natural sound recordings for the most realistic listening experience they use asti patented adaptive soundtm technology that listens and responds to background disturbances the asti product family delivers relaxing and peaceful environment wherever it is needed sound sleep contains new generation of adaptive sound technology for better response to wide range of background noise its 10 high quality soundstories provide rich and natural sound environments in small package and include controls to personalize the sounds to your individual preferences two operating modes combine with tactile buttons and display lighting controls for easy operation at night sound sleep comes with selection of ten extremely high quality primarily natural sound recordings higher quality than professional cd recordings three richness settings give sound sleep broad range of additional sounds to augment any soundstory they enhance noise masking ability and avoid the annoying monotony and repetition of the short and often synthetic recordings found in competing products included sounds oceano rainfallo meadowo brooko waterfallo white noiseo meditationo traino cityo fireplacesound sleep has been designed to be compact and convenient to put on the smallest night stand you can turn off the display lights easily adjust settings and select soundstories in very little light or total darkness despite its diminutive size sound sleep provides incredibly robust audio letting the sound of nature gently rock you to sleep","title":"SOUND+SLEEP (Ecotones Duet) Adaptive Sound Machine, Black","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":56444},"price":119.28,"brand":"Adaptive Sound Technologies, Inc."}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004D6426K","answerTime":"2012-11-08","unixTime":1352361600.0,"question":"can woman use it also","answer":"yes woman can use it to for her protein and calorie needs if she looking to gain weight its has the amino acids to help perserve muscle gains and carbs for glycogen replenishment","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Body Fortress Super Mass Gainer, Chocolate, 2.25 Pounds","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":2043},"price":25.6,"brand":"Body Fortress"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004ECU1W2","answerTime":"2012-11-11","unixTime":1352620800.0,"question":"does it really come with free dark rustic pipe with any order","answer":"when got this pipe there wasn an offer associated with it but its been my experience with amazon retailers that if an offer is given you take screen capture just in case they forget or try to play the semantics game","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"quality wooden churchwarden made by","title":"F.e.s.s. Long Churchwarden Tobacco Pipe","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":13885},"price":25.89,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004EXOFVY","answerTime":"2012-10-11","unixTime":1349938800.0,"question":"want to return it should have read the reviews first it does painfully crush the feet also there was no user manual with it will return it","answer":"it absolutely crushes the feet but mine also didn shut off or do any other settings than one so would return it returned mine as well","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"this is the only shiatsu foot massager applied with kneading rolling to relief tension and fatigue with traditional shiatsu and reflexology therapy carepeutic hand touch kneading rolling shiatsu foot massager is ergonomically designed with foot shape and nerve points to activate joints and maximize relaxation on your foot the kneading and rolling nodes are set just right to the point that can efficiently improve blood circulation ease painful and tired feet as well as legs getting painful sore tired feet the carepeutic hand touch kneading rolling shiatsu foot massager is designed to bring you reflexology and deliver acupressure shiatsu massage to soothe your tired aching feet and relieve tightness and pain this kneading and rolling shiatsu massager is specially designed according to the sensitive points of the lumbar region calf region and the sole of foot as well as the reflecting characters of the complicated nerve system it includes comfortable clipping board and rolling devices to deliver an effective healthy massage for dual foot single foot and sole regions with the high raised rolling balls four automatic massage programs the elastic step width of kneading discs and three adjustable speeds it brings the most powerful soothing shiatsu massage on the bottoms of your feet and relieves tightness on your ankles it fits most sizes of feet it is lightweight and portable with built in carry handle for easy transport the touch panel massage program control on the case is plus","title":"Carepeutic KH385L-B Deluxe Hand-touch Kneading Rolling Shiatsu Foot Massager for Tension and Fatigue Relief, Black","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":57641},"price":149.95,"brand":"Carepeutic"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004F4PR6Y","answerTime":"2012-12-07","unixTime":1354867200.0,"question":"does this machine work for doing permanent makeup","answer":"don know would go and speak with professional at shop who has done this before have absolutely no experience with permanent makeup think it would work but be sure to speak with someone who has that experience","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"this is brand new top quality customized tattoo kit all items in package are selected base on suggestions of experienced artists all basics you need to start your tattooing hobby are included tattoo needles are gas sterilized we using the 45 copper threads strand silicone insulated tattoo gun power cord which offer very good conductivity and flexibility here are the items in kit and their major specifications super popular 10 layer warp coils tattoo machine gun super popular 10 layer wrap coils craved antique tattoo gun with snake leather pattern wrap craved antique grip matching style with gun purple grip with rod ul listed digital power supply set operating at 110v 220v output 2vdc to 20vdc foot control power switch very unique high quality silicone insulated tattoo power cord alloy round tips and alloy magnum tips 3r 5r 5m 7m on each 18 disposable tips set of tools 50 cushion ring and rubber band 50 artists selected disposable needles 3rl 5rl 7rl 9rl 5rs 7rs 9rs 5m1 7m1 9m1 for each size set of 10 colors 3oz 10ml base inks red brilliant blue white black green golden dark brown light pink sky blue royal violet 100 ink cups and cup holder printing transfer oil packs of ointment pairs of rubber glove practicing leather like sheet with tiger and dragon pattern tutoring cd","title":"Deluxe Tattoo Kit 2 Machine Gun Power Supply Needles 11 Inks (Double Black Inks) K03","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":9850},"price":43.99,"brand":"ordertattoo"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004FOQJJS","answerTime":"2012-12-27","unixTime":1356595200.0,"question":"is it led","answer":"yes","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"experience the powerful healing of 10 000 lux light therapy with this safe soothing and measurably effective sad seasonal affective disorder treatment system sleek compact and portable this best seller sets new standard for convenience and ease of use light therapy especially for sadalthough it true that sad is caused by not getting enough light during winter shorter days and long lasting cloud covers you can fix the problem just by sitting near an ordinary lamp studies show that what you need is short blue light wavelength like the omega 470 nm delivered at super bright 10 000 lux intensity it can banish sad symptoms such as depression low energy anxiety carb cravings insomnia and decreased sex drive in as little as 15 minutes day it can also help your body regulate melatonin production getting you back into healthy sleep rhythm and it clinically proven to be just as effective as expensive risky anti depression drugs adjusts to your needs life and styleat just inches the omega can go anywhere you do place it next to you while you re eating breakfast exercising watching tv or working at computer it also comes with an adapter and carrying pouch for taking to the office or on trips out of town fully programmable the omega allows you to adjust the light intensity and session time until you find the therapy program that works best for you safety and performance assuredthe omega emits specific blue light wavelengths while filtering out harmful uv rays it comes with year seller warranty","title":"Omega Sunlight SAD Light Therapy (Seasonal Affective Disorder) Super Bright","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":19415},"price":48.3,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004IAM2TA","answerTime":"2012-12-19","unixTime":1355904000.0,"question":"oops is this keyboard compatible with mac computer","answer":"purchased this keyboard for my pc but have recently replaced the pc for mac book pro the keyboard works great with my mac when first connected it got message that the mac didn recognize the keyboard probably because it not one of the better known makes this was followed by drop down list to select country for the keyboard clicked united states and it connected immediately great keyboard","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"the ezsee by dc usb large print keyboard provides easy to see computer keys with extra large key legends for greater visibility and efficiency designed using low profile keys with the largest legends available on the market high quality keyboard rated for greater than 10 million keystrokes","title":"New Improved EZSee by DC - USB Wired Large Print Keyboard - White Letters on Black Keys - Jumbo Oversized Letters \/ Characters - Great in Dim Lighted Areas and Not so Bright Rooms - Visually Impaired, Low Vision, Low Light, Perfect for Seniors and People with Bad Eye Sight","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":58791},"price":29.94,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004LTYIXQ","answerTime":"2012-11-30","unixTime":1354262400.0,"question":"does the cold amp allergy medication contain aspirin","answer":"no it does not","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"","title":"PACK OF 3 EACH QC COLD &amp; ALLERGY PE 24TB compare TO Actifed&reg; &amp; Sudafed PE&reg; Sinus + Allergy","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":42442},"price":6.67,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004PTI1CQ","answerTime":"2012-10-31","unixTime":1351666800.0,"question":"like to see copy of the label and ingredients is that possible","answer":"this site shows the label www herbalprovider com","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"the garcinia gold trade advantagegarcinia gold trade by nutrigold reg is formulated using super citrimax reg patented all natural non stimulant safe and effective fruit extract used for satiety at lower dosages and weight loss at higher dosages extracted from the south asian fruit garcinia cambogia garcinia gold trade contains standardized levels of hydroxycitric acid hca which have been clinically shown to provide satiety help manage appetite and inhibit fat production without stimulating the central nervous system about garcinia super citrimax reg super citrimax reg is an all natural safe and effective fruit extract garcinia cambogia extracted from the south asian fruit garcinia cambogia super citrimax reg is standardized to 60 hydroxycitric acid hca which has been clinically shown to suppress appetite inhibit fat production increase fat burning and increase weight loss without stimulating the central nervous system super citrimax reg has been determined gras generally recognized as safe by group of independent leading toxicologists garcinia gold trade works by inhibiting the enzymes that convert carbohydrates into fat if not utilized for energy carbohydrates are converted into fat and stored in the body super citrimax reg inhibits the conversion of carbohydrates into fat and promotes an increase in the formation of stored energy as glycogen this also signals the brain to turn off hunger signals published peer reviewed clinical studies show that super citrimax reg increases fat oxidation burning as well as brain serotonin levels neurotransmitter involved in mood sleep and appetite control which may help address many of the emotional issues overweight people face including binge eating and mood disorders these statements have not been evaluated by the fda this product is not intended to diagnose treat or cure any disease","title":"Garcinia Cambogia Extract - 100% Pure Garcinia Cambogia GOLD - 500 mg, 180 Veggie Capsules (Clinically-Proven, Multi-Patented, Water-Soluble SuperCitrimax&reg; 60% HCA Extract for Weight-Loss)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":1459},"price":25.22,"brand":"Nutrigold"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004PTI1CQ","answerTime":"2012-10-30","unixTime":1351580400.0,"question":"does this product contain potassium","answer":"it does","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"the garcinia gold trade advantagegarcinia gold trade by nutrigold reg is formulated using super citrimax reg patented all natural non stimulant safe and effective fruit extract used for satiety at lower dosages and weight loss at higher dosages extracted from the south asian fruit garcinia cambogia garcinia gold trade contains standardized levels of hydroxycitric acid hca which have been clinically shown to provide satiety help manage appetite and inhibit fat production without stimulating the central nervous system about garcinia super citrimax reg super citrimax reg is an all natural safe and effective fruit extract garcinia cambogia extracted from the south asian fruit garcinia cambogia super citrimax reg is standardized to 60 hydroxycitric acid hca which has been clinically shown to suppress appetite inhibit fat production increase fat burning and increase weight loss without stimulating the central nervous system super citrimax reg has been determined gras generally recognized as safe by group of independent leading toxicologists garcinia gold trade works by inhibiting the enzymes that convert carbohydrates into fat if not utilized for energy carbohydrates are converted into fat and stored in the body super citrimax reg inhibits the conversion of carbohydrates into fat and promotes an increase in the formation of stored energy as glycogen this also signals the brain to turn off hunger signals published peer reviewed clinical studies show that super citrimax reg increases fat oxidation burning as well as brain serotonin levels neurotransmitter involved in mood sleep and appetite control which may help address many of the emotional issues overweight people face including binge eating and mood disorders these statements have not been evaluated by the fda this product is not intended to diagnose treat or cure any disease","title":"Garcinia Cambogia Extract - 100% Pure Garcinia Cambogia GOLD - 500 mg, 180 Veggie Capsules (Clinically-Proven, Multi-Patented, Water-Soluble SuperCitrimax&reg; 60% HCA Extract for Weight-Loss)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":1459},"price":25.22,"brand":"Nutrigold"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004Q7CK56","answerTime":"2012-12-07","unixTime":1354867200.0,"question":"does anyone have long term experience with using steam on hardwood floors most reviews were ok with using on wood but they were short term","answer":"don know what you consider long term but have been using steam on my hardwood floors for about years now with absolutely no problems the key to it is the fact that you are using steam and not lots of water that is pooling on your hardwood floors","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Hoover TwinTank Steam Mop, WH20200","salesRank":{"Home &amp; Kitchen":881},"price":68.99,"brand":"Hoover"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004QWUEAY","answerTime":"2012-10-18","unixTime":1350543600.0,"question":"have the same question as above is the battery of this groomer dual voltage 110 220v","answer":"yes it is dual voltage","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"give yourself the perfect haircut with ease and accuracy when you use the philips norelco do it yourself hair clipper with full range of length settings including clean shave attachment 180 degree rotating head and comb that follows the contours of your head the do it yourself hair clipper lets you shave or trim your hair without help even in hard to reach areas","title":"Philips Norelco QC5550 Do-It-Yourself Headgroomer","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":40131},"price":58.99,"brand":"Philips"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004TD23W2","answerTime":"2012-12-09","unixTime":1355040000.0,"question":"overall do you get 40 mouthguards it says 10 pack pack of but then states that for 19 99 you pay mouthguard","answer":"you only get 10 mouthguards for the 19 99 box that pack of stipulation is definitely confusing the directions say to wear the mouthguard for only days but get about week depending on how much my life makes me grind my teeth my dentist was going to charge me over 550 for one made for me but just can figure out how would make it clean enough after awhile so these fit the bill for me and it will be quite awhile before amass 550 worth of these hope this answers your question","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"plackers 10 count grind no more dental night prate counter used for bruxism which is more commonly known as teeth grinding or clenching the first disposable and ready to use night guard offers cost effect counties solution that provides exceptional comfort prate count ion and hygiene one size fits all may be worn on upper or lower teeth meets the demanding needs of both clinchers grinders no boiling cutting or molding required it an instant fit every time wear up to days and throw away","title":"Plackers Mouth Guard Grind No More Night Time Use - 1 package (10 count)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":2866},"price":16.62,"brand":"Plackers"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004UBB2NO","answerTime":"2012-10-23","unixTime":1350975600.0,"question":"does this hook up to computer","answer":"no it does not but is great product","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"monster point tattoo stencil thermal copiereliminate cross contamination and transfer sketches and prints effortlessly onto thermal paper with this simply effortless monster point tattoo stencil copier machine lightweight and compact machine spans small area of 11 easily fitting into limited desk or work area using a4 and a5 paper sizes the copier allows the artist to create thermal copy in matter of seconds machine is compatible for 110 and 120 volts and ships with us prong plug however an appropriate region plug can be switched out upon special request while ordering combined with its user friendly touch pad interface and speedy conversion process the monster point stencil copier serves as fundamental commodity for the tattoo parlour includesmonster steel copier10 spirit thermal transfer papers 11 oz stencil staytattoo design instructional dvd","title":"Monster Point Tattoo Drawing Design Thermal Stencil Copier FLASH Printer Hectograph Machine","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":171193},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004UJ0UFM","answerTime":"2012-11-04","unixTime":1352012400.0,"question":"is it better than iosol","answer":"have not used iosol personally so can say yes or no have never heard of it befote either get the books about iodine from mark sircus or dave brownstine lugols iodine has been in use for around 200 years and is well proven nascent is said to be the easiest for your body to make use of go on youtube and search for 73leo73 for couple of videos about different iodine formulas","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"nascent iodine is consumable iodine in its atomic form rather than its molecular form it is an iodine atom that has an incomplete number of electrons it is paramagnetic what does that mean well it means that the iodine atoms can hold an electromagnetic charge while this all might sound little like flashback to chemistry class the most important thing to understand is that nascent iodine has huge energy release when consumed this charged state is held by the atom until diluted in water and consumed whereby it gradually loses energy over hour time span during this time nascent iodine is recognized by the body as the same iodine that is produced by the thyroid and is absorbed effortlessly by the body","title":"LL's Magnetic Clay Nascent Iodine - 1 Oz.","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":6338},"price":28.99,"brand":"sallyashop"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004UQ6NP6","answerTime":"2012-12-08","unixTime":1354953600.0,"question":"will this product work in europe","answer":"yes the power converter built into the plug is dual voltage you ll need the pin converter though","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Braun 3Series 320S-4 Shaver","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":2672},"price":51.34,"brand":"Braun"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004UVYOZW","answerTime":"2012-11-24","unixTime":1353744000.0,"question":"does this product remove facial hair specifically from the upper lip","answer":"yes you can use the legend on the face and on the upper lip suggest using it on the slower first speed and always make sure the area you are epilating is clean if the hair is very fine and peach fuzzy and if it has hard time removing it then you will probably need the epilady esthetic as that is specifically made for peach fuzz type of hair and will remove any thin hair the legend has hard time removing hope this helps","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"the legend is epilady newest full size rechargeable epilator allows you to remove hair all over your body for up to weeks the legend is the latest in the line of epilady best selling legend epilators it can be used corded or cordless with the same power and efficiency either way the perfect angle guide puts the user in the perfect angle for epilation for great results the first time removes hair safely from the arms legs underarms bikini and face do not use around the eyes smooth quiet and efficient the legend is our best epilator yet kit includes adapter perfect angle guide storage pouch cleaning brush and instruction manual one year manufacturer x2019 warranty","title":"Epilady EP-810-33A Legend 4 Full-Size Rechargeable Epilator","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":11887},"price":67.8,"brand":"Epilady"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004VEXRTW","answerTime":"2012-11-17","unixTime":1353139200.0,"question":"hi is this product gluten dairy free","answer":"believe it is but not sure it doesn say anything anywhere on the box would check the website for this product and maybe even call their customer service 8774335642","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"isn it time you ended your child poor sleep cycle ozzzz sleep aid for children is pediatrician recommended and was developed with the assistance of pediatrician by mother and registered nurse safe and effective ozzzz is an all natural gentle chamomile and melatonin formula see the remarkable difference that good night sleep can have on your whole family don suffer another night 30 fruit flavored ez melts fast dissolving tablets healthy blend of 5mg melatonin and 2mg chamomile free of most known allergens including gluten wheat nuts dairy soy corn yeast fish egg each batch tested for safety and active ingredient strength combination and strength of ingredients helps children to sleep naturally and stay asleep the statements regarding these products have not been evaluated by the food and drug administration these products are not intended to diagnose treat cure or prevent any disease you should not use this information to diagnose or treat any health problems or illnesses without consulting your pediatrician or family doctor please consult your doctor with any questions or concerns you might have regarding you or your child condition individual results may vary","title":"OZzzz's Sleep Aid for Children-30 Fruit Flavored, EZ Melts (fast-melting) Tablets. Pediatrician Recommended. All Natural. Guaranteed Results!","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":939},"price":10.0,"brand":"OZzzz&#39;s"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004X4TSWK","answerTime":"2012-12-30","unixTime":1356854400.0,"question":"does this fit an elongated toilet","answer":"it fit my regular sized oval toilet inside bowl not including rim measures 14 in length and would fit regular round toilet it sits on the bowl not the seat and there is not that much overage when placed on my toilet bowl","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"convenient on off control clip fits most standard toilets aids in relieving the discomfort of perinea conditions such as hemorrhoids menstrual cramps bladder or prostate infections includes 2000ml solution bag","title":"Nova Ortho-Med Sitz Bath","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":9464},"price":12.73,"brand":"Nova Ortho-med"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B004Y99EO6","answerTime":"2012-12-17","unixTime":1355731200.0,"question":"can this be used by more than one child","answer":"yes the tips are removable at the push of button and there is one hole on the unit to store one tip any additional tips can be put in separate container like cup it comes with regular tip and tip that is usually used for braces they sell replacement tips on amazon just make sure you get the correct ones","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"waterflosser for kids is ideal for kids to 12 the waterflosser is compact simple effective colorful and fun to use","title":"Waterpik Waterflosser for Kids, White","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":1289},"price":39.99,"brand":"Waterpik"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0050D26TU","answerTime":"2012-12-19","unixTime":1355904000.0,"question":"can bluette be used in he top loaders","answer":"use it in my he top loader dilute cup bluette with cup of water mix separately to dilute and then gradually add to water dispenser as it fills the cycle","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"whitens white clothes and brightens colors safely why bluing white fabric turns yellow or gray with age and repeated washings bluing restores the sparkling whiteness works on synthetics as well as natural fabrics without harming fibers like bleach can bluette laundry bluing can be traced back more than hundred years it functions as laundry whitener because trace of blue in the wash will enhance white and light colored articles making them appear whiter and brighter try bluette for whiter whites it is safe and gentle even on delicate fabrics laundry bluing is added at the start of the wash cycle unlike other laundry products that are added during the final rinse cycle","title":"Bluette Concentrated Liquid Laundry Bluing 16oz - Pack Of 3","salesRank":{"Home &amp; Kitchen":56612},"price":10.95,"brand":"Malco"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0052456US","answerTime":"2012-10-31","unixTime":1351666800.0,"question":"is this product septic safe","answer":"we have septic tank have been using unstoppables for about year and have had no problems to date","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Downy Unstopables In Wash Fresh Scent Booster 13.2 Oz","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":91},"price":1.81,"brand":"Downy"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0055NW8SE","answerTime":"2012-12-29","unixTime":1356768000.0,"question":"does it fit an iphone with case","answer":"indeed use it with samsung galaxy nexus with case that much bigger phone","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"soft microfiber pouch will keep your small electronics in place and clean and polish without scratching the delicate screen","title":"Casabella I Pouch","salesRank":{"Home &amp; Kitchen":81333},"price":5.93,"brand":"Casabella"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B005BDAFK6","answerTime":"2012-10-31","unixTime":1351666800.0,"question":"does this work under worldwide xff1f like 220v voltage xff1f usually travel outside us want to know does it work in different voltages","answer":"yes it is rated for 110v 240v ac 50 60hz","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Philips HP6512 Satinelle Soft Epilator, White\/Purple","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":95797},"price":59.99,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B005DKIJAA","answerTime":"2012-11-05","unixTime":1352102400.0,"question":"is the battery replaceable by owner","answer":"hi joanne think so have not done it yet as have own this watch for only few months it is standard cr 2032 type of battery and it is accessible with small phillips screwdriver if there is rubber gasket for the seal just make sure it seats properly into the grooves when you put the cover back on hope this helps","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"chest strap size 38 to 51 inches 96 5cm to 130cm needs to be worn fairly snug to the body to ensure precise heart rate measurement analog signal transmission average and maximum heart rate individual training area settable training area alarm training area times below within above training zone suggestions automatic fitness level including interpretation and vo2max pc ready fitness test with interpretation max oxygen breath volume vo2max basal metabolic rate bmr active metabolic rate amr calculated maximum heart rate and suggested training zones calorie consumption in kcal calorie consumption basic turn over bmr and activity amr in kcal fat consumption in or oz heart rhythm led red or green date day of week time 12 24 hr alarm clock lap times 50 for each training recall of all of them or each one display of lap time and average heart rate pulselight water resistant 30m stainless steel casing usb inferface stopwatch power saving mode after mins inactivity","title":"Beurer PM62 Heart Rate Monitor","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":244663},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B005FCBB7E","answerTime":"2012-11-14","unixTime":1352880000.0,"question":"is the white handle included as shown in the photo and how many do you get for the 30 99","answer":"the white handle is included and forms the cap over the brush when not in use","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"1614pnab part 1614pnab proxabrush traveler tapered 36 bx by sunstar","title":"1614PNAB Part# 1614PNAB - Proxabrush Traveler Tapered 36\/Bx By Sunstar Americ...","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":80410},"price":39.99,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B005HJ9KC8","answerTime":"2012-12-29","unixTime":1356768000.0,"question":"will this fit wine bottle","answer":"not quite just the very top sticks out and the bag is much wider","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"perfect packaging alternative for items that requires more natural look it has drawstring closure at the top of the bag 100 jute fabric bag with jute rope can be used packing gift bag and is reusable the bag have competitive price with high quality this product is non washable","title":"High Quality Jute\/Burlap Drawstring Bag Eco Friendly Natural 10x14- Set of 6 - CarryGreen Summer Collection Sale","salesRank":{"Kitchen & Dining":12071},"price":18.98,"brand":"CarryGreen"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B005JF4IG8","answerTime":"2012-12-16","unixTime":1355644800.0,"question":"is this waterproof","answer":"no it isn the case can be taken off and washed but the actual pillow its self is not waterproof if it gets wet it will absorb the water and swell up","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"memory foam is renown for its effective qualities of pressure reduction and support this is very luxurious version of tempurpedic neck pillow that retails for 99 the super soft velour cover is removable and can be laundered unlike other cut memory foam pillows this is molded and has soft doughy feel the memory foam is naturally dust mite resistant it sleeps cool and adapts to your body temperature includes one travel size 10 12 contour memory foam pillow","title":"Z&reg; by Malouf TRAVEL SIZE Memory Foam Molded Contour Neck Pillow - Luxurious Washable Cover","salesRank":{"Home &amp; Kitchen":33309},"price":29.99,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B005NICH1O","answerTime":"2012-12-26","unixTime":1356508800.0,"question":"is it non toxic to pets","answer":"am only guessing here because cannot be 100 sure but used it around both of my cats and both of my dogs have of each and they were all completely fine try keeping animals off the carpet an impossible feat in itself am assuming it is totally safe","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"new proprietary advanced pet formula includes ingredients that penetrate deep into the carpet fiber and eliminate the most stubborn pet stains and odors and deter re soiling","title":"Hoover 2X PetPlus Pet Stain &amp; Odor Remover 32 oz, AH30325","salesRank":{"Home &amp; Kitchen":5561},"price":15.09,"brand":"Hoover"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B005PUZZR8","answerTime":"2012-11-10","unixTime":1352534400.0,"question":"is the charger dual voltage","answer":"the power adaptor has two prongs and it is 120v input and 5v output if it would help can take picture of the charger for you","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Remington MB4040 Lithium Ion Powered Men's Rechargeable Mustache Beard and Stubble Trimmer","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":1025},"price":38.44,"brand":"Remington"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B005QSI8A0","answerTime":"2012-11-18","unixTime":1353225600.0,"question":"can this scale be placed on carpet","answer":"no im pretty sure theres no scale that could be placed on carpet and giv an accurate measurement","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"digital bathroom scale that is accurate and quickthe digital bathroom scale sb925 by mira is ultra sleek and stylish as it is accurate blending beautifully with any decor so much more than just beautiful bathroom scale it is also high tech workhorse designed with state of the art sensors detecting the exact moment you step on this digital bathroom scale this accurate bathroom scale has every key feature you ll ever need at modest price the mira digital bathroom scale is designed with large easy to read lighted display that is visible even in rooms with dim lighting it good looks also last long time the mira sb925 digital bathroom scale is so rugged and dependable that it arrives at your doorstep with two year warranty purchase this super accurate bathroom scale with complete confidence your satisfaction is important to us we provide easy access to customer support for this digital bathroom scale so that help is only phone call or email away if you need it though it highly likely that you won mira guarantee 100 mira guaranteed product satisfaction is assured for the mira sb925 digital bathroom scale customer satisfaction is our highest priority contact us via phone or email anytime for support with our products","title":"MIRA Instant On Digital Bathroom Scale with lighted display","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":10013},"price":19.95,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B005SS5GSK","answerTime":"2012-12-10","unixTime":1355126400.0,"question":"is the instructional dvd amp manual included with the true back device","answer":"when you purchase it brand new there is manual purchased it used and it wasn included","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"product descriptiontrue back is natural drug free convenient and affordable treatments take only few minutes and can be performed in the comfort of one home office or workplace without disrobing true back is officially listed as nonpowered orthopedic traction device true back relieves the body of daily stress tension and discomfort the unique patented design of true back is quite simple while lying on the device the spine floats in the center channel please see diagram below the thirty suspension points molded into the center rails support your body weight and create pressure to the muscles which are located each side of the spine musculoskeletal system the pressure enables the muscles to relax which increases blood flow while lying on true back the individual is passively stretched in opposite directions while being supported in the correct position stretching is natural just take look at dog or cat when they wake up their natural instinct is to stretch true back should not be considered for only correcting problems and rehabilitation it is also very effective at preventing possible problems active and athletic people appreciate the many benefits that true back offers the device should be used before physical activity and especially afterwards this will reduce and prevent the buildup of lactic acid true back has an enduring effect unlike some other devices such as magnets and hot and cold packs treatments take only few minutes and can be performed in the comfort of your home office or work place without disrobing","title":"True Back Orthopedic Traction Device - As Seen on Tv","salesRank":{"Industrial & Scientific":4408},"price":99.95,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B005XYFCN8","answerTime":"2012-11-13","unixTime":1352793600.0,"question":"is 220v model available","answer":"that is the model purchased recently have thoroughly enjoy it good luck","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"our newest diffuser if you enjoy essential oils you ll love this diffuser the ultimate in safe and complete diffusion of essential oils into your room atmosphere far superior to other diffusers new classic design for use in your home spa or office this uses no heat or air pumps which can seriously damage the chemistry of essential oils and operates with safe low voltage direct current they harness the science of ultrasound to deliver micron sized essential oil droplets so fine that within moment of leaving the diffuser the cool mist becomes vapor incorporated into the atmosphere and spreading evenly throughout your room our new relaxing led colored light enhances the mood while diffusion continues adjustable timer settings and mist settings can last the entire night without refilling when the water level gets low the diffuser shuts itself off","title":"Classic Ultrasonic Aromatherapy Diffuser","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":37798},"price":63.95,"brand":"Hubmar"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B005YXLMO6","answerTime":"2012-12-30","unixTime":1356854400.0,"question":"does this have iron do not want the one with iron","answer":"does this have iron want without iron","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"product descriptionwithout iron 90 servings","title":"Isotonix Multivitamin 10.6 oz 300 grams(90 Servings\/bottle)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":77986},"price":48.95,"brand":"Isotonix"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0061JPJ28","answerTime":"2012-10-24","unixTime":1351062000.0,"question":"the description says anti perspirant deodorant but the product photo is for deodorant are we sure that this is the anti perspirant deodorant","answer":"do not sweat under my armpits with this product however do not apply large amount because it will rub off on your shirt","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Dove Men + Care Antiperspirant, 2.7 Ounce, Twin Pack","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":392},"price":7.35,"brand":"Dove"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0067BB9FQ","answerTime":"2012-11-21","unixTime":1353484800.0,"question":"started using this oral device weeks ago but every time use it got all wet my face gets wet does this normal","answer":"no it not normal put the jet tip the part that squirts into your mouth before you turn on the irrigator and turn the irrigator off before you take out the jet tip bend over the sink and let your mouth hang open as you work the jet tip from tooth to tooth you can watch the yukky stuff that was stuck between your teeth and under your gums falling out as you use the irrigator this way to clean your mouth it nice knowing that stuff isn there any more and you ll find you still get stuff out of your mouth with the irrigator even after brushing and flossing","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Panasonic Oral Irrigator EW-DJ10-A","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":1036},"price":36.36,"brand":"Panasonic"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B006JTNX3M","answerTime":"2012-12-13","unixTime":1355385600.0,"question":"does it weigh in ounces","answer":"no it dont weight in ounces it weighs in kilo or pounds and it does weigh more then just even ex you dont getjust like 122 or 123 lbseven unless you are you would get 122 or 145 depending on your weight","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"the gurin precision plus digital bathroom scale is the ideal way to track your weight loss this user friendly scale features auto on technology to give you quick easy to understand results four precision sensors provide an accurate measurement each time you step onto the scale silver toned non slip platform whether you re personal trainer or just trying to get back in shape this gurin scale is an affordable solution for keeping up with weight management goals","title":"Gurin Precision Digital Bathroom Scale with Ultra Wide Platform and Auto-on Technology, 440-Pounds","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":107885},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B006L4IHBS","answerTime":"2012-12-13","unixTime":1355385600.0,"question":"would like to see ingredient list and nutritional information protein calories additives etc","answer":"url go to that link and click on the nutrition information","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"vital whey is delicious 100 natural nutritional protein perfect for adults and children vital whey is the finest biologically active non denatured native whey protein it is minimally processed to maintain the full range of all the fragile immune modulating and regenerative components naturally present in fresh raw milk in addition to its many health promoting properties it is great way to manage hunger and sustain good energy levels vital whey is the best choice for the parent in search of the healthiest snack for themselves and their children as well as the athlete looking for the perfect pre and post workout supplement or anyone interested in optimal health when you try it you will agree it is the vital whey to health","title":"Vital Whey Natural 21 oz(600g)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":16552},"price":39.16,"brand":"Well Wisdom"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B006O3MPHI","answerTime":"2012-12-14","unixTime":1355472000.0,"question":"does it have an auto shut off when the water runs out","answer":"the blinking means its off and out of water","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"this ultrasonic aromatherapy diffuser with million ultrasonic vibrations per second is aromatherapy nebulizer system that also ionizes essential oil molecules into the air using heat free diffusion method while enhancing an oil biological effects ideal for improving the atmosphere of any home or work space the aroma lumin also produces wonderful lighting effect with changing colors filtered through the bubbling water","title":"Aroma Lumin - Ultrasonic Aromatherapy Diffuser","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":93147},"price":31.45,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0073C8CVW","answerTime":"2012-12-27","unixTime":1356595200.0,"question":"what type of battery nicd li ion etc is in the mangroomer scruff sculptor pro stubble trimmer also is the charger","answer":"sorry forgot to mention about the battery and charger it is permanent battery the only thing with the mangroomer is cord to plug in from the mangroomer to socket in the wall it takes approximately hours for full charge from empty and lasts about one hour of non stop grooming such as if you are doing body hair","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"","title":"MANGROOMER Scruff Sculptor PRO Stubble Trimmer with Electric Length Controls, Whisker Belly and Power Burst","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":34465},"price":42.83,"brand":"MANGROOMER"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B00767NBUQ","answerTime":"2012-12-09","unixTime":1355040000.0,"question":"do this come with any warranty","answer":"no warranty that know of but the first one that received had disassembled ball bearing of unique design they requested that return the defective unit with prepaid ups label returned the unit and new one appeared pretty rapidly all of that said the do not stock any parts the bearings that might give problems some day and nothing of the sort and in the right size seems to exist in the us these were made on the shop floor no one stocks them if have another bearing fail expect to replace all with something available here which will likely require new link arms not big thing but and it is neat toy it will be presented as christmas present","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"just have seat on the padded thigh rests position yourself over the dildo and use your own body movement to control the thrusting speed and depth the love glider arrives fully assembled and all you have to do is attach one of the two included flexible dildos to get started on the ride of your life enjoy being penetrated by the ribbed penis attachment or use the tapered anal probe for some backdoor action powered by your own body motions there are no cords to get in the way or power outlets to look for the love glider is compatible with most vac lock dildos for wide array of pleasure possibilities penis and tapered dildo are about in length","title":"Love Glider Sex Machine","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":139260},"price":329.95,"brand":"LoveBots"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B00767NBUQ","answerTime":"2012-12-09","unixTime":1355040000.0,"question":"do you ship to australia","answer":"buyer of one is answering the question these are made in china don know what the importer may be doing with the rest of the world amazon needs to forward the question to them","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"just have seat on the padded thigh rests position yourself over the dildo and use your own body movement to control the thrusting speed and depth the love glider arrives fully assembled and all you have to do is attach one of the two included flexible dildos to get started on the ride of your life enjoy being penetrated by the ribbed penis attachment or use the tapered anal probe for some backdoor action powered by your own body motions there are no cords to get in the way or power outlets to look for the love glider is compatible with most vac lock dildos for wide array of pleasure possibilities penis and tapered dildo are about in length","title":"Love Glider Sex Machine","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":139260},"price":329.95,"brand":"LoveBots"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B00767P2OO","answerTime":"2012-11-19","unixTime":1353312000.0,"question":"hi is the material of the scene setter plastic sheet which can be folded similar to table runner","answer":"hi see my review posted on november 2012 commented about the material of this item karin","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"mickey mouse is the best loved male mouse in the world this mickey mouse scene setter is great value as it contains scene setters at 59 inches 32 inches large banner at 44 inches 16 inches and fun cut outs 16 inches 10 inche","title":"Disney Mickey Mouse Scene Setter Decoration Set (Blue\/Green) Party Accessory","salesRank":{"Toys & Games":1773},"price":6.98,"brand":"Disney"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B00772AQD0","answerTime":"2012-11-24","unixTime":1353744000.0,"question":"is there anything else in these capsules aside from aloe vera","answer":"yes rice brand oil softgel capsule gelatin glycerin water beeswax and silca all of these were listed as other ingredients","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"now foods aloe vera 000 mg softgelsaloe vera contains variety of nutrients including vitamins minerals enzymes and amino acids in particular aloe vera is source of mucopolysaccharides also known as glycosaminoglycans gags which are thought to be its active component numerous scientific studies have demonstrated the ability of aloe to support the healing process in addition aloe vera has been shown to support healthy digestive system","title":"NOW Foods Aloe Vera Gels, 5000mg Softgels, 100-Count","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":3094},"price":8.04,"brand":"Now Foods"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B007ADLJ0A","answerTime":"2012-10-01","unixTime":1349074800.0,"question":"is the product septic system safe","answer":"really not sure ve read on other websites that the kaboom bowlblaster powder product is septic safe as well as their tile cleaner so one could assume this liquid bowlblaster is safe as well if you like to be completely certain would suggest contacting the makers thru the product website www kaboomkaboom com","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"kaboom xae bowlblaster xae toilet bowl cleaner changes color when clean goes in purple turns green when clean sparkling clean scent 100 tough xae","title":"Kaboom BowlBlaster Liquid Toilet Bowl Cleaner, 24 oz","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":19075},"price":10.0,"brand":"Kaboom"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B007HWJIWA","answerTime":"2012-10-29","unixTime":1351494000.0,"question":"do the maxi hair plus veggie caps with biotin work better than maxi hair maximized vitamins for making your hair grow","answer":"the gluten free veggie caps acutally made my hair shed","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"target mins are complexed with specific free form amino acids and other carriers for optimum mineral transport","title":"Country Life Maxi Hair Plus Biotin 120 VegiCaps","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":3044},"price":16.4,"brand":"Country Life"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B007URMD4C","answerTime":"2012-12-27","unixTime":1356595200.0,"question":"does it come with car charger","answer":"mine arrived yesterday 12 26 2012 did not come with car charger","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"the intellicharge i4 is universal automatic smart charger compatible with almost all types of rechargeable batteries thus eliminating the need to own several chargers the i4 is able to automatically identify li ion ni mh and ni cd rechargeable batteries and apply an appropriate charging mode constant charge current cc constant charge voltage cv and trickle charge each of the i4 has four microcomputer controlled charging slots which are capable of monitoring and charging the same type of batteries additionally yellow and blue power charging status indicator lights could visibly indicate battery status and charging process features xb7 capable of charging batteries simultaneously xb7 automatically identifies li ion ni mh and ni cd rechargeable batteries xb7 features three charging modes cc cv and trickle charge xb7 automatically detects battery status and selects the appropriate voltage and charge mode xb7 color led displays charging progress for each battery xb7 automatically stops charging when complete xb7 features reverse polarity protection xb7 designed for optimal heat dissipation xb7 certified by both rohs and ce specifications input voltage ac 110 220v 50 60hz or dc 12v dimensions 139mm xd7 96mm xd7 36mm weight 156g without batteries and power cord compatible with li ion 26650 22650 18650 17670 18490 17500 17335 16340 rcr123 14500 10440 ni mh ni cd aa aaa sc","title":"Sysmax\/Nitecore Intellicharge I4 V2 Universal 4 Channel Li-Ion Ni-Cd Ni-MH Smart Charger","salesRank":{"Kitchen & Dining":58767},"price":13.7,"brand":"Nitecore"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B007ZN5ATQ","answerTime":"2012-11-29","unixTime":1354176000.0,"question":"is it possible to purchase soft travel case for my tooth brush kit didn get one with my essence","answer":"found soft travel case at walgreen drug store that just bits my philips sonicare","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Philips Sonicare HX5610\/30 Essence 5600 Rechargeable Electric Toothbrush, Frustration Free Packaging","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":58},"price":39.95,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B007ZRZSR6","answerTime":"2012-12-17","unixTime":1355731200.0,"question":"is this product waterproof just got back from the dentist and they recomended water flosser to use in the shower","answer":"the only reason can think you would use in shower is to keep overspray from getting everything wet like the mirror so use it in shower without water running","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"update nov 2012 we have corrected the problem we saw with some of our inventory anyone with an issue can request free replacement at no cost lightweight and rechargeable the professional oral irrigator by toilettree products provides and easy and effective way to support proper teeth and gum health at home daily irrigation helps reach places brushing simply can not promoting cleaner teeth and healthier gums the result an incredibly clean fresh happy mouth irrigating is easier and less abrasive than string floss this irrigator is powerful water jet which helps remove debris deep between teeth and reduces the risk of bacteria build up in crevices and below the gum line add in little mouthwash for an extra fresh feeling irrigating is great for hard to reach spots especially for people with bridges and braces the irrigator comes with rotating interchangeable nozzles great for multiple users three operating modes are useful for varying oral care needs normal soft and pulse pulse mode comfortably massages the gums the extra large reservoir is removable and easy to refill cordless design powered by rechargeable batteries we have redesigned our original oral irrigator to eliminate problems that some of our customers experienced if you have one of our original oral irrigators and would like to exchange it for brand new redesigned rechargeable irrigator at no cost please just email us we stand 100 behind our customers and products","title":"Professional Rechargeable Oral Irrigator with High Capacity Water Tank by ToiletTree Products","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":93715},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0080DTSYI","answerTime":"2012-12-26","unixTime":1356508800.0,"question":"is there an unscented version of this product hydrogen peroxide doesn stink and don need unnecessary scents","answer":"presently there is no unscented version of course they may come out with one","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Lysol Power and Free Multi-Purpose Cleaner With Hydrogen Peroxide Citrus Sparkel Zest Scent, 22 Ounce","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":6443},"price":5.41,"brand":"Lysol"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0082EB7V2","answerTime":"2012-12-09","unixTime":1355040000.0,"question":"will this refill fit the standard original evercare lint roller","answer":"they fit the 10 year old evercare roller found in my junk drawer so my guess is yes they should fit","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"aboutevercare extra sticky roller refill 60 sheets pack 180 sheets america selling lint roller50 stickier new dry cleaner grade tape extra sticky 60 sheets pick up lint dirt dandruff and pet hair zip strip technologytotal 29 8ft 4in per rollcompared to evercare classic or standard lint roller based on independent tests results following astm guidelines and specifications for evercare lint roller products individual results may vary based on various factors made in usa","title":"Evercare EXTRA Sticky Roller REFILL (3 PACK - 180 Sheets)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":6590},"price":16.5,"brand":"Evercare"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0082ZP0WI","answerTime":"2012-10-24","unixTime":1351062000.0,"question":"can this unit be used with headphones","answer":"the nomad doesn have headphone jack it does have mini input jack so you can plug in an external audio source like an mp3 player and play the music through the nomad speakers the larger unit does have both internal and external jacks so you would be able to use headphones with that model","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"SOUND+SLEEP Nomad Adaptive Sound Machine for Travel, Black","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":17602},"price":89.99,"brand":"Sound Sleep"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B008510GY6","answerTime":"2012-11-19","unixTime":1353312000.0,"question":"can you pick different flavors","answer":"nope","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"14 pack variety set of beamer ultra premium hookah molasses 50 gram boxes includes one of each of all 14 flavors double apple lemon mint tropical punch rose cherry strawberry party on the beach strawberry banana berry mix blueberry mint triple grape watermelon and citrus punch huge clouds amazing taste 100 amazing taste 100 ultra premium 100 tobacco free 100 nicotine free 100 tar free compare to hookah tobacco at fraction of the cost very strong flavor amazing tobacco flavor without tobacco tar or nicotine comes in sealed bag to maintain freshness and also comes with re sealable box to store it when not in use look for the other 20 flavors of beamer ultra premium hookah flavors in sizes 50 gram box 100 gram metal tin 250 gram metal tin 1000 gram package the beamer molasses company was founded to give the discerning hookah smoker premium quality smoking experience beamer huge burst of flavor and enormous clouds of smoke provide the ultimate hookah enjoyment if you want to escape to amazing taste and enormous clouds then beamer hookah molasses is the choice to make perfect ingredients perfect blend perfect choice beamer uses only the finest herbs and flavors each flavor is crafted to provide the greatest taste and huge clouds of enjoyment each smoking experience comes with the best taste imaginable and clouds of smoke beamer is constantly working on new flavors that will excite your taste buds beamer is made with high amount of flavor concentration with the new no smoking law in many states beamer molasses can be smoked in businesses and restaurants because it is not tobacco depending on your states laws make the switch to beamer beamer is manufactured in the united states and packaged and labeled for maximum shelf appeal and convenience of use beamer supports the united states economy","title":"14 Flavor Variety Pack - 1 of each flavor of - Beamer&reg; Ultra Premium Hookah Molasses 50 Gram boxes! Huge Clouds, Amazing Taste!&reg; 100 % Tobacco, Nicotine &amp; Tar Free but more taste than tobacco! Compares to Hookah Tobacco at a fraction of the price! GREAT TASTE, LOTS OF SMOKE &amp; SMELLS GREAT!!! Proudly made in the USA!","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":28294},"price":29.25,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0086VI9TE","answerTime":"2012-12-08","unixTime":1354953600.0,"question":"is there difference between brush head hx6013 64 and hx6013 82","answer":"yes both brush heads can be viewed on the amazon website hx6013 82 has smaller head","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Philips Sonicare HX6013 Proresults Brush Head, Standard, 3 Pack","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":159},"price":22.85,"brand":"Philips"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0086VI9UI","answerTime":"2012-12-08","unixTime":1354953600.0,"question":"is there difference between brush head hx6013 64 and hx6013 82","answer":"yes both brush heads can be viewed on the amazon website hx6013 82 has smaller head","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Philips Sonicare HX6013 Proresults Brush Head, Standard, 3 Pack","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":159},"price":22.85,"brand":"Philips"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B008H0BHES","answerTime":"2012-11-27","unixTime":1354003200.0,"question":"are these extentions remy","answer":"they re human hair if that what you re asking they re nice thin but nice they took few months to get here though recommend ordering with rush delivery","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"these hair extensions are made from 100 real human hair the hair is extremely soft silky and straight finally clip in extension that allows you to have fuller longer and more beautiful hair easily attached with great look in minutes great news finally an extension that can be straightened waved or curled use low heat the extensions being offered are of the highest quality material and contain no synthetic hair or animal hair the extensions are made from 100 real human hair this gives the extensions longer life which means brighter longer lasting shine every pack of hair will contain weft pieces which will include one wide clips two wide clips two wide clips one wide clips two wide clip the hair is shipped locally from within the us the hair will be shipped within business day of the sale we are 100 committed to providing you with star customer service on every transaction before during and after the sale thank you kingshair save seller","title":"20&quot; Inch Silky Straight Clip on in Human Hair Extensions, 10pcs, 100g, Color #613 (Platinum Blonde)","salesRank":{"Beauty":146976},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B008I20LJ2","answerTime":"2012-12-27","unixTime":1356595200.0,"question":"can this product be made to work with kindle fire since lack iphone","answer":"it seems to be an apple related product so works with ipad but kindle fire unless you get specific software for it would say no","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Zeo Sleep Manager Pro","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":41302},"price":100.0,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B008IW15XI","answerTime":"2012-12-01","unixTime":1354348800.0,"question":"does this plug into the wall","answer":"yes the electric cord is attached to pillow the control is also attached by cord on the control is switch for heat switch for the direction the massage heads turn and circular button for speed of massage heads","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"the quality life kneading massage car cushion has rotating shiatsu heating heads the soothing heat helps blood circulation it targets muscle stiffness and tension where you need it allows multiple massage positions for neck lower upper back shoulders lumbar area abdomen calf and more it weights only pounds stripe is built in the back of the pillow easy to use control panel allows multiple massage speeds with unlimited intensity options for customized massage experience heating is optional with heat levels when it is overheated the built in overheat protection device will turn off machine automatically after long day sit down and relax your muscles with neck back and shoulder massagers from the quality life we have full inventory of body massagers with heat therapy","title":"The Quality life Portable Shiatsu Massage Cushion Pillow","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":188142},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B008KMM468","answerTime":"2012-11-29","unixTime":1354176000.0,"question":"does this item come with bottles like it shows in the picture","answer":"no the purchase amount is for one bottle","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"the average american diet is filled with extremely acidic foods including soda coffee jam white bread white pasta cheese and dairy our bodies have to fight extra hard to maintain the optimal neutral acidity level if our blood is too acidic our bodies will remove calcium from bone and other sources to neutralize the acid chronic forms of acidosis may even affect proper weight control metabolic efficiency and athletic performance supplement facts serv size capsule 500 mg serv per container 60 amount per serving alkalete blend 500 mg calcium carbonate potassium hydroxide potassium chloride magnesium hydroxide daily value not established other ingredients magnesium stearate silicon dioxide","title":"PH Enhancer","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":134322},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B008RYTAD4","answerTime":"2012-11-20","unixTime":1353398400.0,"question":"is this manufactured by sonicare","answer":"no","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"the diamondtm ultrasonic toothbrush uv sanitizer delivers 30 000 powerful strokes per minute for dazzling white teeth powerful ultrasonic action provides extreme clean healthier gums by removing plaque below the gum line where normal bristles can reach two minute auto timer and 30 second alerts let you know when to change your brushing quadrant modes with led indicator whitening gentle and massage the diamondtm has an extended charge for travel and the ergonomic and waterproof design makes it comfortable and convenient to use uv sanitizer bulb kills up to 99 of bacteria in minute auto timed session the sanitizer chamber stores up to brush heads your diamond toothbrush box includes ultrasonic toothbrush handle uv sanitizing charger base brush heads","title":"Diamond Ultrasonic Toothbrush with UV Sanitizer","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":93745},"price":121.59,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B008SAM9EE","answerTime":"2012-11-12","unixTime":1352707200.0,"question":"will this hurry cane tip fit on other canes","answer":"no","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"","title":"Replacement Feet for the HurryCane","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":98771},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B008XI4AQQ","answerTime":"2012-11-15","unixTime":1352966400.0,"question":"is the bottle 33 oz or is the combined total of all bottles 33 oz","answer":"each bottle is 33 oz the bottles last about month","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"what is limu seaweed harvested from pollution free waters in the south pacific used as nutritional and medicinal staple for 000 years it not juice and it not superfruit either it something much more unique premium seaweed in bottle at the core of the limu experience is limu original our flagship product that will help you to feel and live better boasting more than 70 essential nutrients including antioxidants polyphenols amino acids glyconutrients vitamins and minerals limu original is nutrition powerhouse tropical blend of mango papaya apple and pear it delicious refreshing and most importantly it offers serious boost to your immune system it 83 pure tongan limu moui it an all natural blend that maintains every vital nutrient just as nature intended it powerful nutrition delivered directly to your body core systems for consistently good health improved joint mobility more restful sleep smoother skin and much more as the lone dietary liquid supplement with limu proprietary fucoidan rich seaweed extract limu original leads the global market","title":"LIMU ORIGINAL~SEAWEED IN A BOTTLE~RICH IN FUCOIDAN ~ FOUR BOTTLES (33.8 FL OZ)","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":55833},"price":182.7,"brand":"Original S.W.A.T."}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0090LXI7W","answerTime":"2012-12-09","unixTime":1355040000.0,"question":"is this weighted so it doesn fall over easily","answer":"it pretty sturdy but not weighted measure your eyeglasses mine did not fit properly","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"our collection of cases may be the most extensive available we offer practically every size of eyewear case from compact reading glass size to oversized cases for wrap around sport glasses and fit overs prices start at only and our range of offerings extend to top quality genuine leather made in italy specialy items such as double cases contact lens cases children cases belt cases custom cases for clic magnetic eyewear and desktop eyeglass holders are all here at the best prices","title":"Desktop Eyeglass Holder w\/ Soft Lining in Brown CA-500","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":75946},"price":12.99,"brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B0093FXMFI","answerTime":"2012-11-19","unixTime":1353312000.0,"question":"is this really for pairs","answer":"no read my review you only receive one and amazon customer service will not help you","answerType":"N","year":2012,"description":"keep feet warm protected and supported around the home in pair of heat holders slipper socks for men with massive tog rating of 34 these seriously chunky slipper socks are made with specifically developed extra heavy bulk yarn with extreme thermal qualities the inside of each fully cushioned sock has been brushed creating an incredibly soft feel ensuring warm air is trapped close to the skin keeping feet warmer for longer the non slip grip on the sole of these slipper socks will help you stay safe around the home","title":"Heat Holders Mens Slipper Heat Holders, Deep Blue, US Shoe Size 7-12, 1 Pair","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":128794},"price":16.55,"brand":"Heat Holders"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B009AH4OR4","answerTime":"2012-11-30","unixTime":1354262400.0,"question":"can you take all three pills at once instead of at each meal","answer":"not doctor and did not conduct the studies but all of the studies say to take the supplement 30 minutes before meal with glass of water there was big german study done and in that the participants took 800mg each time ve been looking for company that sells 800 mg without fillers but can find one thought that this company produced one based on their product description but discovered that was not the case when got the 30 bottle","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"NatureWise UltraPure GCA Green Coffee Bean Extract Made With 100% Pure GCA, 90 Veggie Caps","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":2013},"price":27.69,"brand":"NatureWise"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B009AH4OR4","answerTime":"2012-12-28","unixTime":1356681600.0,"question":"if you are not hungry can you take the pills not eat and have them work or do you need food for them to work","answer":"don know how to answer but would be cautious of possible stomach ache","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"NatureWise UltraPure GCA Green Coffee Bean Extract Made With 100% Pure GCA, 90 Veggie Caps","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":2013},"price":27.69,"brand":"NatureWise"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B009EPIMCU","answerTime":"2012-10-17","unixTime":1350457200.0,"question":"is it safe for people with diabetes and hypertension","answer":"what suggest is you contact this company will order only this product from this company because as nurse practitioner was impressed behind the transparency that was exhibited by all of the research stats what to expect all of the ingredients etc that was included with the product that said contact them and request information about the product then consult your primary care provider hope that helps am still seeing results daily have energy have decreased appetite and am losing weight was skeptical at first but am soooo glad found this product to help me lose weight also exercise and take this in conjunction with the raspberry ketones by greenweb","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"svetol green coffee goldwhy is svetol green coffee gold the best green coffee product the only product that contains full 400 mg of svetol green coffee extract per capsule svetol is an award winning green coffee extract proven in research studies svetol weight loss effects have been clinically proven on humans in double blind placebo controlled clinical trials svetol is clinically proven to improve lean mass to fat mass ratio by the only gc extract with clinically proven bio availability and absorption manufactured without additives preservatives or artificial ingredientslearn and comparemost green coffee products on the market are made with generic gc extracts the products that do mention svetol on their labels contain only 25 svetol mixed with 75 generic gc extracts the worst are the products that don even mention the of chlorogenic acids svetol vs gca vs other green coffee extracts svetol is lot more expensive than gca and several times more expensive than generic green coffee extracts svetol has been proven in research studies gca has been proven in and generic green coffee extracts just make projections and assumptions from borrowed research svetol is an extract ofcoffea canephora robustawhereas gca and generic green coffees are extracts ofcoffea arabica cheaper variety clinical trials using svetol were performed in europe on large groups very reliable whereas the single clinical trial using gca was performed in india on just 16 people cross over study design with small population is not very reliable svetol is standardized to 50 total polyphenols 45 chlorogenic acids 10 caffeoylquinic acid and less than caffeine whereas gca is standardized to 50 chlorogenic acids and less than caffeine generic gc extracts are standardized from to 50 ca or not standardized at all safety warning do not exceed recommended dose pregnant or nursing mothers children under the age of 18 and individuals with known medical condition should consult physician before using this or any dietary supplement","title":"NutriGold Pure Green Coffee Bean Extract, 90 Vegetarian Capsules","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":9986},"price":24.99,"brand":"Nutrigold"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B009EPIMCU","answerTime":"2012-12-29","unixTime":1356768000.0,"question":"is it alright to also take nutrigold garciana cambosia along with green coffee bean extract","answer":"don know but have gotten really good help from the nutrigold company with my other questions when called them at 800 973 1485","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"svetol green coffee goldwhy is svetol green coffee gold the best green coffee product the only product that contains full 400 mg of svetol green coffee extract per capsule svetol is an award winning green coffee extract proven in research studies svetol weight loss effects have been clinically proven on humans in double blind placebo controlled clinical trials svetol is clinically proven to improve lean mass to fat mass ratio by the only gc extract with clinically proven bio availability and absorption manufactured without additives preservatives or artificial ingredientslearn and comparemost green coffee products on the market are made with generic gc extracts the products that do mention svetol on their labels contain only 25 svetol mixed with 75 generic gc extracts the worst are the products that don even mention the of chlorogenic acids svetol vs gca vs other green coffee extracts svetol is lot more expensive than gca and several times more expensive than generic green coffee extracts svetol has been proven in research studies gca has been proven in and generic green coffee extracts just make projections and assumptions from borrowed research svetol is an extract ofcoffea canephora robustawhereas gca and generic green coffees are extracts ofcoffea arabica cheaper variety clinical trials using svetol were performed in europe on large groups very reliable whereas the single clinical trial using gca was performed in india on just 16 people cross over study design with small population is not very reliable svetol is standardized to 50 total polyphenols 45 chlorogenic acids 10 caffeoylquinic acid and less than caffeine whereas gca is standardized to 50 chlorogenic acids and less than caffeine generic gc extracts are standardized from to 50 ca or not standardized at all safety warning do not exceed recommended dose pregnant or nursing mothers children under the age of 18 and individuals with known medical condition should consult physician before using this or any dietary supplement","title":"NutriGold Pure Green Coffee Bean Extract, 90 Vegetarian Capsules","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":9986},"price":24.99,"brand":"Nutrigold"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B009GRFZGM","answerTime":"2012-12-02","unixTime":1354435200.0,"question":"does this battery have protection circuit to limit overcharge and overdischarge the answer is yes these are protected cells received and tested the batteries writing on the label says the ic for protection against short circuit overcharge","answer":"there doesn appear to be any protection built into these batteries took voltage measurement while had these sitting out of circuit and they had just over volts several days after gave them little time in the charger","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"","title":"2Pcs 3.7V 1200mAh Li-on Rechargeable Batteries","salesRank":"x","price":5.89,"brand":"WorthTrust"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B009I2MYE6","answerTime":"2012-11-29","unixTime":1354176000.0,"question":"do power swabs work on bonded teeth","answer":"yes they do they work on any dental surface","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"consumers who purchase and use the highly innovative power swabs system can expect to receive many short term and long term benefits after the first five minutes of use they will see immediate noticeable results without any procedural teeth sensitivity the product even works to removes stains from crowns and other cosmetic restorations then seven days after system use is completed consumers can expect to see smile that is much whiter and healthier looking also because stain out swabs work to pre removed the stains and prevent teeth sensitivity our customers should expect that their teeth will remain whiter longer and feel great","title":"Power Swabs Whitening Kit","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":135245},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B009VQT53M","answerTime":"2012-11-15","unixTime":1352966400.0,"question":"are these excedrin from the new production since the recall","answer":"haven looked for date on the bottle assumed that these were of current date what have noticed is that the coating on the tablet has changed so maybe they are of the newer production line","answerType":"?","year":2012,"description":"the neurologist recommended otc and first non prescription medicine approved by the fda to treat all the symptoms of migraine active ingredients acetaminophen 250 mg purpose pain reliever aspirin 250 mg purpose pain reliever caffeine 65 mg purpose pain reliever aid","title":"Excedrin Migraine 300 Coated Caplets","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":3992},"price":11.99,"brand":"Excedrin"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B009VRCHTK","answerTime":"2012-12-21","unixTime":1356076800.0,"question":"is this shipped discretely in plain package live in an apartment so many people see my packages on the shelf","answer":"hi just got mine in the mail it came in white package that you would usually get with an amazon purchase just says dst brands as the sender and had my address on it when opened its shipping bag it was wrapped in what would consider brown butcher paper","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"this high quality rabbit vibrator can offer you great stimulations while you re letting that warm soothing bath flow over you imagine letting the water consume you while you stimulate yourself to orgasm with this vibrator with waterproof rabbit vibe you can have pleasures no matter where you are","title":"Trinity Waterproof Rabbit Vibe","salesRank":{"Health & Personal Care":94902},"price":12.99,"brand":"XR Brands"}
{"questionType":"yes\/no","asin":"B009WR73X4","answerTime":"2012-11-30","unixTime":1354262400.0,"question":"does this swivel sweeper have the touchless dirt tray","answer":"it has dirt tray that falls into the trash can when you squeeze the release buttons","answerType":"Y","year":2012,"description":"deluxe cordless swivel sweeper bonus mini sweepers deluxe cordless swivel sweeper the deluxe unit of the unbelievable cordless swivel sweeper the cordless swivel sweeper has taken the nation by storm selling millions of units since its release with its amazing quickness light weight ease of use and its ability to clean on all sides at the same time nothing can compete it picks up everything from dust to the big stuff while combining the benefits of vacuum with the ease of swiffer weighing only pounds and having low profile design the swivel sweeper goes anywhere you can slide it under furniture with ease and clean the stairs quicker than ever it swivels 360 degrees and picks up messes like you wouldn believe the swivel sweeper is great for picking up crumbs dirt pet hair dust and more use it in the kithen family room dining room and bathroom on tile carpet hardwood and more the rechargeable battery lasts over 45 minutes on single charge features swivels 360 degrees cleans on all side cordless operation weighs only pounds uses powerful volt rechargeable battery bonus mini sweepers included all types of floors wood tile carpet vinyl includes cordless swivel sweeper rechargeable battery and charger brush cleaning tool and cover bonus mini sweepers","title":"Deluxe Cordless Swivel Sweeper with Bonus Mini Sweepers","salesRank":{"Home &amp; Kitchen":610879},"price":"x","brand":"x"}
